<Encounter>
  <Faction>Revoran</Faction>
  <Step>0</Step>
  <Name>First Contact</Name>
  <DescriptionText>Your forces have discovered a small planet in the Revoran system. It is home to a pre-warp species that appears to be in the Rocket Age. They are broadcasting a primitive radio signal into space but it does not seem to have any specific target. </DescriptionText>
  <MessageList>
    <Message>
      <Index>0</Index>
      <text>pulse pulse. pulse pulse pulse. pulse pulse pulse pulse pulse. pulse pulse pulse pulse pulse pulse pulse.  </text>
      <ResponseOptions>
        <Response>
          <Text>Dispatch a diplomatic shuttle to land upon the planet's surface and greet the alien people</Text>
          <FailIfNotAlluring>true</FailIfNotAlluring>
          <FailIndex>1</FailIndex>
          <SuccessIndex>2</SuccessIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Encode a radio message with a greeting from your leaders and send it to the planet</Text>
          <RequiredTech>Xeno Linguistics</RequiredTech>
          <FailIndex>3</FailIndex>
          <SuccessIndex>4</SuccessIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Encode a radio message with 11 similar pulses and transmit it to the planet</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>5</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Do Nothing.</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>6</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
      </ResponseOptions>

    </Message>
    <Message>
      <!--fail!! -->
      <Index>1</Index>
      <text>You send a diplomatic shuttle to the planet's surface. Within a few minutes of its arrival, its emergency beacon activates and begins broadcasting a mayday plea. The voice of a panicked-sounding crew member can be heard over the sound of alien screams and gunfire. "We terrified them!" he cries. "They're attacking us! They are more powerful than we first ima..." The message ends there.</text>
      <EndTransmission>true</EndTransmission>
    </Message>
    <Message>
      <!--Success because alluring!! -->
      <Index>2</Index>
      <text>You send a diplomatic shuttle to the planet's surface. Your diplomat reports that upon landing, his shuttle was immediately surrounded by local armed forces. However, as our diplomat opened the hatch to his shuttle and showed himself to the people there, a silence fell over the crowd. There was no violence. Our diplomatic team is now working with the local people, who call themselves the Revorani, to master their language and deciper their customs.
      
We shall have further opportunities to interact with the Revorani in the near future.      
      </text>
      <EndTransmission>true</EndTransmission>
    </Message>

    <Message>
      <!--fail! -->
      <Index>3</Index>
      <text>The message that you broadcast in the Revoran system seems to have been received. You are receiving a response back. A lyrical but chaotic language of confusing clicks, whistles and other odd sounds can be heard through the static of the message. Your computers cannot discern its meaning, but clearly the natives are attempting to communicate with you.
      
A study of Xeno Linguistics will help us understand what they are saying to us.
      </text>
      <ResponseOptions>
        <Response>
          <Text>Do Nothing.</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>6</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Dispatch a diplomatic shuttle to land upon the planet's surface and greet the alien people</Text>
          <FailIfNotAlluring>true</FailIfNotAlluring>
          <FailIndex>1</FailIndex>
          <SuccessIndex>2</SuccessIndex>
        </Response>
      </ResponseOptions>
    </Message>
    <Message>
      <!--Success! -->
      <Index>4</Index>
      <text>The message that you broadcast in the Revoran system seems to have been received and understood. Your computers are able to decipher its meaning.

"In the name of all the people of the planet Revoran, we greet you. We invite you to come to our planet in peace."
      
      </text>
      <ResponseOptions>
        <Response>
          <Text>Do nothing</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>6</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Dispatch a diplomatic shuttle to land upon the planet's surface and greet the alien people</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>2</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
      </ResponseOptions>

    </Message>
    <Message>
      <Index>5</Index>
      <text>You broadcast the original message along with your message containing the next prime number in the sequence. Soon after, you beging to recieve a stream of data from the planet. Music, images, video recordings, mathematical formulas -- the natives are attempting to communicate with you.
   
A study of Xeno Linguistics will help us understand what they are saying to us.   
      </text>
      <ResponseOptions>
        <Response>
          <Text>Do nothing</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>6</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
        <Response>
          <Text>Dispatch a diplomatic shuttle to land upon the planet's surface and greet the alien people</Text>
          <DefaultIndex>1</DefaultIndex>
        </Response>
      </ResponseOptions>

    </Message>
    <Message>
      <Index>6</Index>
      <text>You decide to leave the planet alone for the time being.</text>
      <EndTransmission>true</EndTransmission>
    </Message>

    
  </MessageList>
  
</Encounter>
