<LocalizationFile>
	<TokenList>
		<Token>
		  <Index>33</Index>
		  <Text>Расы с высокоэффективным метаболизмом каждый ход потребляют на 20% меньше еды</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>35</Index>
		  <Text>Прожорливые расы едят очень много, потребляя на 20% больше еды каждый ход</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
			<Index>52</Index>
			<Text>Зоркие</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>53</Index>
			<Text>Обостренные чувства и осознание своего окружения позволили этой расе сосредоточиться во время боя. Снаряды, выпущенные из их оружия, имеют на 20% повышеную точность.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>54</Index>
			<Text>Слепые</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>55</Index>
			<Text>Расы, у которых в процессе эволюции слабо развились органы чувств, терпят поражение в космических боях. У снарядов, выпущенных из их оружия, увеличивается шанс промаха на 20%.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>71</Index>
			 <Text>Благодаря рациональному и скоординированному использованию ресурсов,эффективные расы сокращают на 25% расходы на обслуживание кораблей и построек.</Text>
		 </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>145</Index>
			<Text>Титан</Text>
		</Token>		 
		<Token>
			<Index>403</Index>
			<Text>Аэропонная ферма</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>404</Index>
			<Text>Аэропоника - это использование атомизированного водяного спрея для доставки питательных веществ растениям, подвешенным в воздухе. Использование этой технологии позволяет растениям расти очень быстро, устраняет необходимость в почве и минимизирует риски заражения микроорганизмами.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>405</Index>
			<Text>+2 еды за ход,10 места в складе.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
			<Index>406</Index>
			<Text>Биосферы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>407</Index>
			<Text>Биосферы - это специальные легкоадаптируемые живые жилища. Биосферы можно строить только на планетах, непригодных для обитания; После их строительства планета становится обитаемой,затем внутри биосферы уже можно строить другие объекты.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
		  <Index>408</Index>
		  <Text>Увеличивает максимум населения; превращает не жилую землю в жилую</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>412</Index>
			<Text>Центр клонирования</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>413</Index>
			<Text>Центры клонирования увеличивают прирост населения планеты с фиксированной скоростью 0,025 за ход.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>414</Index>
			<Text>+0.025 популяции за ход</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>418</Index>
			<Text>Сверхглубокая шахта</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>419</Index>
			<Text>Сверхглубокие шахты чрезвычайно эффективны при быстрой добыче полезных ископаемых из глубины на уровне ядра планеты, но наносят ущерб окружающей среде. Даже при использовании лучших экологических технологий плодородие планеты упадет почти до нуля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>420</Index>
			<Text> (-3) к плодородию за постройку, +15 к продукции, +50 места в складе</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>421</Index>
			<Text>Лаборатория генетики</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>422</Index>
			<Text>Производительность этого объекта генетических исследований зависит от количества колонистов, выделенных для выполнения задачи, обеспечивая +0,2 исследования на каждого назначенного колониста.Это также дает дополнительный бонус к еде для колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>423</Index>
			<Text>+0.2 к науке за задествованного колониста, +1 еды за ход</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>427</Index>
			<Text>Имперский банк</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>428</Index>
			<Text>Имперский банк увеличивает эффективность сбора налогов с планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>429</Index>
			<Text>+50% к сбору налогов, +0.5 кредитов за колониста</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>430</Index>
			<Text>Имперские учреждения</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>431</Index>
			<Text>Имперские офисы допускают прямое налогообложение граждан, обеспечивая дополнительный доход.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>432</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 кредитов за колониста, +10% к налогам</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>439</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная шахта</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>440</Index>
			<Text>Позволяет обстреливать вражеские корабли самонаводящимися ракетами, значительно повышая обороноспособность планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>441</Index>
			<Text>Запускает на орбиту 3 ракеты большой дальности.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>448</Index>
		  <Text>+20 места в складе, +1 Инфраструктура, +0.1 Продукции за богатство</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>452</Index>
			<Text>Исследовательская лаборатория</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>453</Index>
			<Text>Исследовательская лаборатория дает колонистам возможность начать изучать их новый дом.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>454</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 к науке за ход, +0.1 к науке за задействованного колониста</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>455</Index>
			<Text>Ангар подъемников</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>456</Index>
			<Text>Управляемые и автоматические подъемники помогают значительно сократить трудозатраты при обустройстве колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>457</Index>
			<Text>+1 продукции за ход, +10 места в складе</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>458</Index>
			<Text>Космопорт</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>459</Index>
			<Text>A space port connects to the orbital star base above and allows for the construction of ships here using materials produced on the planet. Provides a 50% bonus to all monetary incomes earned on this planet.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>460</Index>
			<Text>+ 50% налоговых поступлений, позволяет строительство судов, помогает в ремонте судов, добавляет складские помещения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>468</Index>
		  <Text>Простое здание с еще более простым предназначением.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>470</Index>
			<Text>Ксеноферма</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>471</Index>
			<Text>Ведение сельского хозяйства на чужих планетах гораздо сложнее, чем просто посадить семена в почву и поливать ростки. Многие планеты могут иметь объективно плодородные почвы, богатые питательными веществами, но в то же время быть несовместимыми с нашими растениями и животными.Ксенофермерство поможет решить эти проблемы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>472</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 еды за задействованного колониста, +25 места в складе</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>473</Index>
			<Text>Ксеношахта</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>474</Index>
			<Text>Ксеношахты - первый шаг на пути к эффективному использованию минеральных богатств планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>475</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 к продукции за задействованного колониста, +30 к складу, +1 к инфраструктуре</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>503</Index>
			<Text>Фонды земледелия</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>521</Index>
			<Text>Наши самые массивные корабли могут принимать суда размером с корвет в эти гигантские ангары. Однако, когда эти "боевые налетчики" уничтожены, они не возрождаются до тех пор, пока базовый корабль не вернется на верфь для пополнения запасов.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>526</Index>
			<Text>Накрывающие щиты I</Text>
		</Token>			
		<Token>
			<Index>552</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутые торпеды</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>553</Index>
			<Text>Электромагнитные импульсные торпеды наносят мощный удар по цели. Если они преодолеют ЭМИ-защиту цели, цель будет выведена из строя на разное время (в зависимости от ее защиты). Диссольверные торпеды запрограммированы на запуск ракет MIRV, которые пройдут мимо цели, развернутся и попытаются поразить ее сзади.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>585</Index>
		  <Text>Конструкция корвета</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>587</Index>
		  <Text>Тяжелые щиты I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>599</Index>
			<Text>Экономические основы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>603</Index>
			<Text>Логистика</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>634</Index>
			<Text>Колониальные щиты</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>635</Index>
			<Text>Удивительно, но защитить целую планету проще, чем защитить весь корабль, потому что нам не нужно беспокоиться об ограничениях массы, размера и мощности при строительстве на твердой земле. В результате получается щит, обеспечивающий некоторую защиту от бомбардировки.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>637</Index>
			<Text>Если мы направим высокоионизированную плазму прямо из реактора корабля через намагниченную систему высокого давления, то мы сможем распылить на наших врагов перегретую энергию с разрушительным эффектом. Очень эффективено против брони, но почти бесполезно против щитов. Теперь мы можем использовать аналогичные методы для создания средней плазменной пушки.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		 <Index>682</Index>
			 <Text>Увеличивает дальность всех сенсоров на 50%.</Text>
		 </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>683</Index>
			<Text>Терраформирование</Text>
		</Token>			 
		<Token>
			<Index>693</Index>
			<Text>Ксено компьютеры I</Text>
		</Token>		 
		<Token>
		  <Index>705</Index>
		  <Text>Ксено шахты I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>910</Index>
		  <Text>Малая энерго-ячейка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>911</Index>
		  <Text>Ячейки собирают и накапливают энергию силовой установки корабля, увеличивая эффективную дальность действия корабля, а также его выносливость в бою.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>917</Index>
			<Text>Создавая массивные проекторы щитов, мы можем окружить целые корабли, включая корабли сопровождения, одним пузырем щита. Затраты на электроэнергию огромны, но наши военные ученые считают, что с помощью этой технологии мы можем создать отличные экранирующие корабли.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>920</Index>
			<Text>Боевой информационный центр</Text>
		 </Token>
		 <Token>
			 <Index>921</Index>
			 <Text>Боевой информационный центр объединяет все функции управления и контроля в единый модуль. Отсюда экипаж может координировать данные датчиков, управлять командами по устранению повреждений, организовывать оборонительные действия на борту и многое другое. Предоставляет широкие бонусы корабля различным системам и маленький пузырь ингибитора деформации.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>925</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль содержит все оборудование, еду и колонистов, необходимые для создания новой колонии в далеком мире, включая небольшое количество колонистов, а также 5 продуктов питания и 5 продуктов для быстрого старта их усилий. Колонизация планеты поглотит корабль, использовавшийся для колонизации, но если на нем есть войска, они высадятся на планете. Грузовые модули увеличивают количество колонистов, которые может загрузить колониальный корабль.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>949</Index>
			<Text>Небольшой щит, разработанный специально для наших истребителей и корветов. Он слабее, чем наш средний генератор щита, но все же обеспечивает важную защиту для малых судов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>951</Index>
			<Text>Этот ангарный отсек поддерживает одновременно один корабль истребительного класса (до 24 слотов). Если истребитель будет уничтожен в бою, он возродится из этого отсека после перезарядки. Вы можете указать, какой из ваших истребителей запускать из этого отсека,на экране дизайна корабля(Верфь).</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>958</Index>
		  <Text>Средняя бронированная энергоячейка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>	
		  <Index>960</Index>
		  <Text>Малая бронированная энергоячейка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>961</Index>
		  <Text>Эта бронированная энергоячейка усилена, чтобы выдерживать больше боевых действий. Она сохраняет то же количество энергии, что и базовые элементы питания, но ее масса увеличивается за счет добавленного усиления.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>980</Index>
		  <Text>Малая красная лазерная пушка</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>981</Index>
		  <Text>Это небольшая лазерная пушка с шарнирным креплением, что делает ее идеальной для кораблей истребительного класса или для обороны крупных кораблей. Она автоматически поражает приближающиеся ракеты, но также может нацеливаться на корабли.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>		
		  <Index>992</Index>
		  <Text>Средняя энергоячейка</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>996</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk2</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>997</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная установка средней дальности на поворотной башне, выпускающая 4 ракеты за залп. Она также имеет систему конечной фазы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>998</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>999</Index>
			<Text>Мы можем улучшить наши ракеты, чтобы они имели большую мощность и скорость.Установленные на большой башне, которая способна запускать больше ракет за залп.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1000</Index>
			<Text>Отсек для тактических ядерных бомб</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1001</Index>
			<Text>Бомбоотсек, позволяющий кораблю поразить планету тактическими ядерными бомбами малой мощности.Плодородие целевой планеты будет снижено. Постоянные бомбардировки могут навсегда снизить рождаемость и даже навсегда изменить климат планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1002</Index>
			<Text>Средний ядерный реактор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1003</Index>
			<Text>Реакторы - это сердце космических кораблей. Эта базовая модель деления обеспечивает умеренный уровень выходной мощности и накопления энергии. Взрывается при уничтожении.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1004</Index>
			<Text>Ядерный реатор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1005</Index>
			<Text>Электростанции - это сердце космических кораблей. Эта базовая модель деления обеспечивает умеренный уровень выходной мощности и накопления энергии. Взрывается при уничтожении.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1006</Index>
			<Text>Склад боеприпасов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1007</Index>
			<Text>Представляет собой корабельные запасы боеприпасов и взрывчатых веществ, таких как пули, ракеты, торпеды, мины и другое специальное оружие. Стандартный скдал, такой как этот, предоставляет капитану безопасное и удобное место для хранения боеприпасов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1008</Index>
			<Text>Малые боеприпасы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1010</Index>
			<Text>Отсек снабжения боеприпасами</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1011</Index>
			<Text>Отсек снабжения боеприпасами позволяет кораблю запускать шаттлы снабжения, заполненные боеприпасами, для пополнения запасов дружественных кораблей. Только один шаттл может быть активен в каждом отсеке одновременно. Шаттлы могут перевозить до 100 боеприпасов за раз.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1012</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелый фазор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1013</Index>
			<Text>Это массивное фазорное орудие имеет жесткое крепление и угол обстрела 45 градусов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1014</Index>
			<Text>Световой фазор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1015</Index>
			<Text>Фазоры - мощное и эффективное оружие направленной энергии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1016</Index>
			<Text>Фотонная турель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1017</Index>
			<Text>Фотонная пушка, установленная на поворотной платформе,очень эффективна в любой боевой обстановке.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1018</Index>
			<Text>Спаренная фотонная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1019</Index>
			<Text>Спаренная фотонная пушка, установленныа в башне с предварительными системами охлаждения для быстрого и непрерывного огня.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1020</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный метатель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1021</Index>
			<Text>Это оружие лучше всего использовать на малых скоростях и близких дистанциях. Более высокие скорости приводят к неэффективному рассеиванию плазмы, и оружие просто бесполезно на расстоянии. Но вблизи оно ужасно.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1022</Index>
			<Text>Большая Пластсталь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1023</Index>
			<Text>Броня из пластстали обеспечивает примерно на 25% меньшую защиту, чем стальная броня,но и весит в половину меньше.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1024</Index>
			<Text>Сдедняя Пластсталь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1025</Index>
			<Text>Броня из пластстали обеспечивает примерно на 25% меньшую защиту, чем стальная броня,но и весит в половину меньше.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1026</Index>
			<Text>Малая Пластсталь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1027</Index>
			<Text>Броня из пластстали обеспечивает примерно на 25% меньшую защиту, чем стальная броня,но и весит в половину меньше.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1028</Index>
			<Text>Поляронная пушечная турель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1029</Index>
			<Text>Вмонтирована в башню поляронная пушка.Обходит щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1030</Index>
			<Text>Спаренная поляронная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1031</Index>
			<Text>Сдвоенные поляронные пушки, установленные на башенной платформе с усовершенствованными системами охлаждения для быстрого и продолжительного огня.Обходит щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1032</Index>
			<Text>Электропровод</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1033</Index>
			<Text>Переносит энергию по кораблю</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1034</Index>
			<Text>Импульсный конденсатор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1035</Index>
			<Text>Это недорогой, но громоздкий электромагнитный конденсатор. Любой корабль, оснащенный импульсными конденсаторами, будет значительно труднее вывести из строя с помощью электромагнитного импульсного оружия. Они также помогают кораблю быстрее восстанавливаться после перегрузок ЭМИ.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1036</Index>
			<Text>Квантовый торпедный аппарат</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1037</Index>
			<Text>Разрушительно мощная энергетическая пушка. Расширение фотонной технологии, этот аппарат стреляет управляемыми энергетическими фотонными снарядами, которые вряд ли будут перехвачены противоракетным оружием.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1049</Index>
			<Text>Этот большой защитный генератор обеспечит существенную защиту наших кораблей на гораздо большей площади, чем предыдущие щиты. Он был разработан для эффективного использования на более крупных кораблях.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1051</Index>
			<Text>Этот средний генератор щита был разработан в ответ на потребность в более мощном, менее энергозависимом защитном модуле для наших кораблей. Он требует меньше энергии, чем наши Магщиты I класса, и обеспечивает гораздо большую защиту, но имеет немного меньшую дальность действия.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>2009</Index>
		  <Text>Балистические орудия имеют 25% шанс пробить щит.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>2116</Index>
			<Text>Схемы этого здания были найдены в руинах родного мира Предтечей.Мы верим, что это устройство позволит нам превзойти наши физические формы. Мы не узнаем, пока не построим и не запустим это.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>2039</Index>
		  <Text>Войска - это вложение, и мы должны защищать эти вложения, предоставляя медицинские учреждения. Эти лазареты можно разместить на станциях или больших кораблях вместе с двумя отрядами, и они будут медленно лечить любые войска. Несколько медпунктов будут иметь акумулятивный эффект.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>2290</Index>
			<Text>Вертикальная ферма</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2291</Index>
			<Text> (+0.1) к плодородию за постройку, +4 еды за ход</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2292</Index>
			<Text>В этой мегаструктуре используются передовые сельскохозяйственные технологии и робототехника для производства огромного количества продуктов питания.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>2249</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Флешетта"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2250</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Флешетта" - оружие ближнего боя. Снаряды, выпущенные из этого ружья, разбиваются при ударе и наносят максимально возможный урон легкобронированным целям.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2251</Index>
			<Text>Ракетный терминал II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4001</Index>
			<Text>Эти отсеки немного больше стандартных. Они хранят более крупные корабли (до 46 слотов) и более эффективно запускают их.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4096</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 исследований за ход</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Oasis-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5092</Index>
			<Text>Оазис</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5093</Index>
			<Text>Резервуар с пресной водой, окруженный плодородной почвой и пышной растительностью.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5094</Index>
			<Text>Производит +0,7 еды за ход</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Underground superstructure-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5095</Index>
			<Text>Подземная суперструктура</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5096</Index>
			<Text>Огромный, искусно спрятанный подземный комплекс, очевидно построенный для укрытия большого населения. Чего могли бояться эти люди с такими передовыми технологиями?</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5097</Index>
			<Text>Обеспечивает приютом большое количество населения</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Ancient megacity-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5098</Index>
			<Text>Древний мегаполис</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5099</Index>
			<Text>Огромное строение в форме пирамиды с продвинутыми туннелями и комнатами. Эти сооружения встречаются на протяжении всей истории многих древних цивилизаций, и все они связаны с пугающе похожими религиозными образованиями.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5100</Index>
			<Text>Обеспечивает жильем большое количество населения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Drone platform-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5101</Index>
			<Text>Платформа дронов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5102</Index>
			<Text>Самоподдерживающаяся планетарная защита. Эта платформа автоматически запускает рой дронов для борьбы с вражескими кораблями вблизи планеты. Для работы требуется технология дронов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5103</Index>
			<Text>Система планетарной защиты. Атакует врагов роем дронов, +50 места на складе</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tim's -->
		<Token>
			<Index>5223</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5224</Index>
			<Text>Ракеты большой дальности предназначены для того, чтобы превосходить по дальности любое другое оружие. Это имеет недостаток, заключающийся в более низкой скорости и маневренности ракет, но он содержит систему с несколькими боеголовками, предназначенную для уменьшения вероятности перехвата.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5225</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5226</Index>
			<Text>Mark II имеет приличную дальность и улучшение урона по сравнению с Mark I.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5227</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5228</Index>
			<Text>Mark III имеет значительную дальность и улучшенный урон по сравнению с Mark II.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5229</Index>
			<Text>Снайперская пушка Гаусса</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5230</Index>
			<Text>Скоростная винтовка Гаусса с большой дальностью действия и большим уроном.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5231</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5232</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, так как предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды Mk1 имеют ограниченную эффективность против брони.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5233</Index>
			<Text>Малая зеленая лазерная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5234</Index>
			<Text>Этот вариант стреляет медленнее, но обладает большей мощностью.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5235</Index>
			<Text>Малая пурпурная лазерная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5236</Index>
			<Text>Этот вариант стреляет очень быстро и может использоваться в качестве точечной защиты против ракет.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5237</Index>
			<Text>Большой фабрикатор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5238</Index>
			<Text>Этот объект представляет собой большой специализированный модуль. Он очень энергоемкий, но производит много боеприпасов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5239</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный склад боеприпасов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5240</Index>
			<Text>Маленькие бронированные ящики для боеприпасов обеспечивают хранение и защиту</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5241</Index>
			<Text>Устойчивая поддержка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5242</Index>
			<Text>Самодостаточность чрезвычайно важна в затяжных боевых ситуациях. Наши инженеры придумали это решение - большой производитель и отсек для хранения</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5243</Index>
			<Text>Второй склад</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5244</Index>
			<Text>Второй склад обеспечивает хранение 150 дополнительной эды и продукции.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5245</Index>
			<Text>+150 места на складах</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5246</Index>
			<Text>Третий склад</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5247</Index>
			<Text>Третий склад обеспечивает хранение еще 150 дополнительных продуктов питания и продукции.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5248</Index>
			<Text>+150 места на складах</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5249</Index>
			<Text>Рентгеновский импульсный луч</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5250</Index>
			<Text>Рентгеновский импульсный луч-турель стреляет смертельными лучами рентгеновских лазеров в быстрой последовательности. Он имеет почти идеальную точность и среднюю дальность, что делает его хорошим оружием для борьбы с истребителями.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5251</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая анти-материальная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5252</Index>
			<Text>Стреляет быстрой очередью из антиматериальных снарядов на большие расстояния. Наносит дополнительный урон щитам и броне,имеет 60% шанс обойти щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5253</Index>
			<Text>Оружие анти-материи I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5254</Index>
			<Text>Путем дальнейшей стабилизации реакций материя / анти-материя нам удалось превратить наши исследования в мощное оружие анти-материи.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5255</Index>
			<Text>Анти-материальный реактор истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5256</Index>
			<Text>Это малая версия анти-материального реактора для конкретных истребителей. У него очень хорошая выходная мощность, но при разрушении он взрывается.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5257</Index>
			<Text>Большая адамантитовая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5258</Index>
			<Text>Невероятно прочный сплав с примесью нейтрония, устойчивый ко всем видам повреждений.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5259</Index>
			<Text>Средняя адамантитовая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5260</Index>
			<Text>Невероятно прочный сплав с примесью нейтрония, устойчивый ко всем видам повреждений.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5261</Index>
			<Text>Малая адамантитовая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5262</Index>
			<Text>Невероятно прочный сплав с примесью нейтрония, устойчивый ко всем видам повреждений.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5263</Index>
			<Text>Большая тритановая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5264</Index>
			<Text>Чрезвычайно высокопрочный и термостойкий сплав.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5265</Index>
			<Text>Средняя тритановая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5266</Index>
			<Text>Чрезвычайно высокопрочный и термостойкий сплав.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5267</Index>
			<Text>Малая тритановая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5268</Index>
			<Text>Чрезвычайно высокопрочный и термостойкий сплав.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5269</Index>
			<Text>Адамантитовые сплавы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5270</Index>
			<Text>Невероятно прочный сплав с примесью нейтрония, устойчивый ко всем видам повреждений.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5271</Index>
			<Text>Тритановые сплавы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5272</Index>
			<Text>Чрезвычайно высокопрочный и термостойкий сплав.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5273</Index>
			<Text>Астероидная база</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5274</Index>
			<Text>Постройте свою собственную базу на астероидах на безопасной орбите вокруг своей родной планеты. В нем представлены все современные товары, к которым вы привыкли. Именно то, что нужно каждому виду гуманоидов!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5275</Index>
			<Text>Гиперскоростная вулкан-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5276</Index>
			<Text>Пушки HV Vulcan стреляют со столь высокой скоростью, что прочность материалов при ударе очень мала по сравнению с инерционными напряжениями. Таким образом, даже металлы при сверхскоростном ударе ведут себя как жидкости. Чрезвычайная сверхскорость приводит к испарению ударника и цели. Они очень эффективны против брони.</Text>
	    </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5277</Index>
			<Text>Малая регенерирующая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5278</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня может выдержать приличный урон. Но где она себя проявляет-так это с нано-ремонтными роботами, которые выпускаются, когда корабль начинает получать повреждения, исцеляя каждый модуль на корабле. Эффекты модулей такой брони акумулятивны, и корабль, оснащенный регенерирующей броней, - это сила, с которой нужно считаться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5279</Index>
			<Text>Регенерирующая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5280</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня может выдержать приличный урон. Но где она себя проявляет-так это с нано-ремонтными роботами, которые выпускаются, когда корабль начинает получать повреждения, исцеляя каждый модуль на корабле. Эффекты модулей такой брони акумулятивны, и корабль, оснащенный регенерирующей броней, - это сила, с которой нужно считаться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5281</Index>
			<Text>Щитовая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5282</Index>
			<Text>Последние достижения в области миниатюризации, защиты и исследования энергии,позволили нам включить небольшой электромагнитный экран в нашу броню.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5283</Index>
			<Text>Малая щитовая плита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5284</Index>
			<Text>Последние достижения в области миниатюризации, защиты и исследования энергии позволили нам включить небольшой электромагнитный экран в нашу броню. Для работы требуется источник питания.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5285</Index>
			<Text>MIRV III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5286</Index>
			<Text>Более совершенные ускорители, более быстрые ракетные двигатели, улучшенные датчики наведения и увеличенная полезная нагрузка позволяют нам разрабатывать новые платформы дальнобойных ракет, которые могут запускать их с большим количеством боеголовок.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5287</Index>
			<Text>Ракетный терминал III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5288</Index>
			<Text>Мы можем разработать лучшую и более крупную ракетную систему "Терминал", которая насытит любую точку обороны большими залпами.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5289</Index>
			<Text>MIRV II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5290</Index>
			<Text>Мы можем разработать более крупную и лучшую систему MIRV, которая будет запускать больше ракет по цели.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5291</Index>
			<Text>Шторм теней</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5292</Index>
			<Text>Скорострельная ракетная платформа с короткими очередями. Особенно смертоносен против небольших быстро движущихся кораблей, он наиболее эффективен как средство борьбы с истребителями и корветами. Он имеет широкий угол наведения и небольшой шанс пробить вражеские щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5293</Index>
			<Text>Шторм теней</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5294</Index>
			<Text>Прототип платформы SRM. Скорострельная ракетная платформа с короткими очередями. Особенно смертоносное оружие против меньших и быстро движущихся кораблей, оно было разработано в основном как средство борьбы с истребителями и корветами.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5295</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5296</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный проектор использует массив узлов генерации плазмы, чтобы проецировать поток высокоэнергетических плазменных оболочек на цель.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5297</Index>
			<Text>Плазменные орудия</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5298</Index>
			<Text>Теперь мы можем создавать более тяжелое плазменное оружие, используя предыдущий ионизированный реактор плазмы и доводя его до новых пределов с более высоким давлением. Однако для срабатывания намагниченной системы давления требуется более стабильная мощность и даже дополнительная мощность реактора.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5299</Index>
			<Text>Улучшения</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5300</Index>
			<Text>Различные варианты исследований для улучшения компонентов корабля, оружия и многого другого.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5301</Index>
			<Text>Пластстали</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5302</Index>
			<Text>Хотя стальная броня стоит недорого, она чрезвычайно тяжелая и значительно снижает маневренность наших кораблей. Сосредоточив наши исследовательские усилия на разработке новых строительных материалов, мы открыли новый сплав. Он немного слабее стали, но очень легко ремонтируется.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5303</Index>
			<Text>Анти-материальный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5304</Index>
			<Text>Проектор антивещества использует массив узлов, генерирующих антивещество, чтобы проецировать на цель шторм очень нестабильных оболочек антивещества. Имеет 25% шанс обойти щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5305</Index>
			<Text>Отсек запуска "Менотиус"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5306</Index>
			<Text>Стартовый отсек Menoetius запускает 4 мины. У них есть 33% шанс пробить даже самые сильные щиты. Как только они пройдут через щит,внутренние реакторы цели вызовут бурную цепную реакцию, заставив их взорваться с огромной силой. Уязвим к ТЗ-оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5307</Index>
			<Text>Анти-материальная торпеда</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5308</Index>
			<Text>Сфера антивещества, содержащаяся в магнитном поле, которое высвобождается при ударе, позволяя антивеществу взорваться. Может быть сбита. Имеет 50% шанс обойти щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5309</Index>
			<Text>Плазменная торпеда</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5310</Index>
			<Text>Сфера плазмы, содержащаяся в магнитном поле, которое высвобождается при ударе, позволяя плазменной сфере взорваться. Может быть сбита.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5311</Index>
			<Text>Оружие анти-материи II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5312</Index>
			<Text>Наши ученые совершили прорыв в своих исследованиях реакций материи и антивещества, предоставив нам доступ к новому оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5313</Index>
			<Text>Пускатель ЭМИ мин</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5314</Index>
			<Text>Мины ЭМИ пытаются поразить уязвимые системы и датчики, чтобы временно остановить атаки кораблей. Уязвим к ТЗ-оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5315</Index>
			<Text>Скорострельные лазеры</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5316</Index>
			<Text>Скорострельные лазеры, или синие лазеры, представляют собой скорострельные лазерные пушки, специально разработанные для истребителей и корветов. Снаряды синего цвета выстреливают в быстрой последовательности, в результате чего оружие переходит в длительный период охлаждения. Идеальное оружие для быстро движущихся кораблей, использующих обстрел.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5317</Index>
			<Text>Пускатель анти-щитовых мин</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5318</Index>
			<Text>Мины-разрушители щитов специализируются на быстром разрушении щитов вражеских кораблей. Уязвим к ТЗ-оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5319</Index>
			<Text>Пускатель мин "Анти-броня"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5320</Index>
			<Text>Противобронные мины оснащены специальными фугасными зарядами, способными пробивать даже самые толстые корпуса. Уязвим к ТЗ-оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5321</Index>
			<Text>Малый минный пускатель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5322</Index>
			<Text>Маленькая минная установка выбрасывает одну фугасную мину. Может быть легко установлена на меньшие корпуса. Уязвим к ТЗ-оружию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5327</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5328</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, так как предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды Mk2 предлагают больший урон и лучшую эффективность поражения брони.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5329</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5330</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, так как предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды Mk2 предлагают больший урон и лучшую эффективность поражения брони.А также взрываются при попадании.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5331</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5332</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, так как предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды Mk2 предлагают больший урон и лучшую эффективность поражения брони.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5333</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5334</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, так как предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды Mk2 предлагают больший урон и лучшую эффективность поражения брони.А также взрываются при попадании.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5335</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая оборонительная турель Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5336</Index>
			<Text>Легкая фазовая защитная турель используется в основном против малых судов, поскольку она предназначена для преодоления щитов цели. Снаряды MkI не очень хороши против брони.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5323</Index>
			<Text>Коса-пулемет H</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5324</Index>
			<Text>Пулемет-коса - отличное средство устрашения для небольших истребителей и стрелкового оружия. Он выпускает почти постоянный поток пуль во все, что осмеливается приблизиться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5325</Index>
			<Text>Коса-пулемет V</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5326</Index>
			<Text>Пулемет-коса - отличное средство устрашения для небольших истребителей и стрелкового оружия. Он выпускает почти постоянный поток пуль во все, что осмеливается приблизиться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5337</Index>
			<Text>Одиночная пусковая установка LRM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5338</Index>
			<Text>Одиночная ракетная установка LRM, удобная и смертоносная.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5339</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5340</Index>
			<Text>Эта платформа MRM запускает залп из 8 ракет по ничего не подозревающим целям. Это оружие может легко сокрушить даже самые мощные системы точечной защиты с его системой конечной фазы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5341</Index>
			<Text>Рельсовая турель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5342</Index>
			<Text>Два рейлгана на поворотной башне. Очень эффективная система вооружения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5343</Index>
			<Text>Снайперская пушка Гаусса AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5344</Index>
			<Text>Скоростная винтовка Гаусса с большой дальностью и уроном, вооруженная бронебойными снарядами.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5345</Index>
			<Text>Снайперская пушка Гаусса HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5346</Index>
			<Text>Скоростная винтовка Гаусса с большой дальностью и уроном, вооруженная фугасными бронебойными снарядами.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5347</Index>
			<Text>Управляемое оружие</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5348</Index>
			<Text>Исследуйте и откройте широкий спектр управляемых систем вооружения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5349</Index>
			<Text>Анти-истребительные ракеты I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5350</Index>
			<Text>Этот набор технологий улучшит нашу способность эффективно сражаться с множеством небольших кораблей на поле боя. В дополнение к ракетам, которые могут быть установлены на наших собственных истребителях, мы также можем производить штормовое оружие для наших более крупных судов, поворотные турели, которые отлично подходят для поражения небольших кораблей противника.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5351</Index>
			<Text>Снайперские системы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5352</Index>
			<Text>Пушка Гаусса - это тип ускорителя снарядов, состоящий из одной или нескольких катушек, используемых в качестве электромагнитов в конфигурации линейного двигателя, который ускоряет ферромагнитный или проводящий снаряд до высокой скорости. Мы можем создавать пушки, которые используют электромагнитные ускорители для стрельбы очень точными и очень скоростными снарядами. Отсюда и название - "Снайпер".</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5353</Index>
			<Text>Снайперские системы AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5354</Index>
			<Text>Теперь мы можем модифицировать наш снаряд пушки  "Гаусса" чтобы использовать компоненты, пробивающие броню, при сохранении почти той же точности и скорости.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5355</Index>
			<Text>Снайперские системы HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5356</Index>
			<Text>Добавление взрывчатки к нашим снайперским пушкам может сделать их еще более смертоносными.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5357</Index>
			<Text>Фазирование защиты I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5358</Index>
			<Text>Турель с поэтапной защитой - это небольшая турель, которая используется в основном для защиты от истребителей.  Снаряды содержат электронные средства измерения, чтобы попытаться измерить частоты щита цели и преодолеть их.  Они могут быть очень эффективными против небольших кораблей, которые, как правило, полагаются на щиты для защиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5359</Index>
			<Text>Фазирование защиты II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5360</Index>
			<Text>Усовершенствования в электронике и баллистике привели к созданию более эффективных снарядов.  Это требует изменения конструкции турелей, но они дают больше шансов поэтапно пройти через броню, а также дают преимущества практически во всех аспектах по сравнению с турелями Mk1.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5361</Index>
			<Text>Фазирование защиты III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5362</Index>
			<Text>Улучшения в электронике и баллистике привели к появлению более эффективных снарядов.  Это требует изменения конструкции турелей, но они дают больше шансов для поэтапного прохождения брони, а также дают преимущества практически во всех аспектах по сравнению с турелями Mk2, включая характеристики взрыва.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5365</Index>
			<Text>Древний столб</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5366</Index>
			<Text>Этот древний столб, кажется, очень ценен. Наши ученые стремятся выяснить, что он делает. Они предлагают вам отправить войска для расследования.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5367</Index>
			<Text>Большой склад</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5368</Index>
			<Text>Некогда заброшенное помещение, сейчас очищено и отремонтировано, этот большой склад обеспечивает хранение на 200 дополнительных продуктов питания и производства.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5369</Index>
			<Text>+200 к месту на складе</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5373</Index>
			<Text>Производственный завод(модуль)</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5374</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль содержит небольшой завод изготовления, обеспечивающий бонус +0,25 к производству на богатство вновь колонизированной планеты. Он также содержит несколько колонистов (меньше, чем обычный модуль колонизации) для запуска колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5375</Index>
			<Text>Репликатор пищевых продуктов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5376</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль содержит небольшой пищевой репликатор, обеспечивающий бонус +0,5 к еде на новой колонизированной планете. Он также содержит несколько колонистов (меньше, чем обычный модуль колонизации) для запуска колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5377</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая гравитонная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5378</Index>
			<Text>Эта тяжелая пушка стреляет смертоносным залпом частиц Гравитона, сжатых в тритановое покрытие высокой плотности.  При ударе это покрытие разрывается, высвобождая чрезвычайно сильный поток гравитационных сил.  Однако щиты уменьшат его разрушительную силу.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5379</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелые гравитонные снаряды</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5380</Index>
			<Text>Оружие, оснащенное гравитационными зарядами, использует антигравитационные генераторы, установленные внутри больших пушек.  Они наносят небольшой урон от удара, но создают прицельный кинетический толкающий эффект, отталкивая любые суда, по которым ведется обстрел.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5381</Index>
			<Text>Спец. оружие</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5382</Index>
			<Text>Оружие, которое не попадает в определенную категорию и не считается нормой.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5383</Index>
			<Text>Исследовательский модуль</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5384</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль содержит небольшую лабораторию, обеспечивающую бонус +0,15 к исследованиям на недавно колонизированной планете.  Он также содержит колонистов для создания колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5385</Index>
			<Text>Малая лаборатория</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5386</Index>
			<Text>Небольшая лаборатория позволяет вашим ученым приступить к исследовательской работе, в основном на новых колониях в суровых условиях.  Обычно она развертывается на колониальном корабле, и ее самым большим преимуществом является то, что она может быть построена даже на непригодной для жизни территонии.  Но стоимость постройки вне колониального корабля высока.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5387</Index>
			<Text>+0.15 к исследованиям, +40 места на складе</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5388</Index>
			<Text>Завод</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5389</Index>
			<Text>Завод-производитель производит всевозможные полезные предметы для раннего развития колонии и обычно размещается на корабле колонизации.  Его самым большим преимуществом является то, что его можно построить даже на непригодной для проживания клетке.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5390</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 продукции за богатство, +30 места в складе</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5391</Index>
			<Text>Пищевой репликатор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5392</Index>
			<Text>Репликатор пищи обеспечивает здоровую, воспроизведенную пищу для колонии.  Количество репликации довольно низкое, но этого может быть достаточно для колонии на ранней стадии, а также может быть достаточно для небольших колоний горняков.  Его самым большим преимуществом является то, что его можно построить даже на непригодной для проживания клетке</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5393</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 еды за ход</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5394</Index>
			<Text>Военный аванпост(модуль)</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5395</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль развернет военный форпост для защиты вашей колонии вместе со скромным количеством колонистов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5396</Index>
			<Text>Модуль ракетной шахты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5397</Index>
			<Text>Этот модуль развернет ракетную шахту для защиты колонии на большом расстоянии, вместе с небольшим количеством колонистов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5398</Index>
			<Text>Казино улья</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5399</Index>
			<Text>Контрабандисты улья</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5400</Index>
			<Text>Ямные рабы улья</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5401</Index>
			<Text>Планетарная оборона III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5402</Index>
			<Text>Планетарная оборона II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5403</Index>
			<Text>Установка планетарной снайперской пушки</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5404</Index>
			<Text>Большая дальность и высокая точность-особенность этого планетарного оружия.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5405</Index>
			<Text>Установка планетарной автопушки</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5406</Index>
			<Text>Мощный и быстрый подавляющий огонь из этих автоматических пушек, должен удержать  любые шатлы от высадки на наши планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5407</Index>
			<Text>Столица Реворан</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5408</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная установка "Облачный пик"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5409</Index>
			<Text>Ракеты "Облачный пик" с наведением "земля-космос".Эти ракеты обладают большой дальностью и способны обеспечить оборонительный контроль над большей частью всей звездной системы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5410</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная защита I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5411</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная защита II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5412</Index>
			<Text>Целесообразней улучшить наши способности к планетарной защите с помощью оружия, которое может отпугнуть захватчиков.  Хорошим началом должна стать серия гигантских пусковых установок ЗРК.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5418</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Дыхание Дракона"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5419</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Дыхание дракона" - оружие ближнего боя.  Горящие плазменные снаряды, выпущенные из этого дробовика, предназначены для перегрева пораженных участков, уничтожая любую защиту, которая может быть у кораблей.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5420</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик с разрывными снарядами</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5421</Index>
			<Text>Оружие ближнего боя.Дробовик оснащен фугасными снарядами, наносящими урон на большой площади.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5422</Index>
			<Text>Высокоскоростной ЭМИ дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5423</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик электро-магнитного импульса, оружие ближнего боя. Он оснащен высокоскоростными эмп-снарядами, способными вызывать збои в электронике вражеских кораблей на короткие промежутки времени.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5424</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик с повторотелем</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5425</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик с механизмом повторного выстрела - оружие ближнего боя и близкий родственник дробовику "Флешетта".  Он стреляет без остановки, пока не закончатся патроны или не уничтожиться цель.  У него также есть способность к пробитию легкой брони..</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5426</Index>
			<Text>Это вооружение восновном имеет большую площать поражения на не большой дистанциии из-за этого его именуют "Дробовиками" .В зависимости от типа используемых боеприпасов они могут наносить разный урон.  Это оружие стреляет быстро и точно.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5427</Index>
			<Text>Дробовики</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5428</Index>
			<Text>ЭМИ дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5429</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик с повторителем</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5430</Index>
			<Text>Разрывной дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5431</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5432</Index>
			<Text>Средняя регенерирующая бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5433</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня может выдержать приличное количество повреждений.И оснащена нано-ремонтными ботами, которые выпускаются, когда корабль начинает получать повреждения, исцеляя каждый модуль на корабле. Эффекты экипированных модулей брони сумируються, и корабль, оснащенный регенерирующей броней, - это сила, с которой нужно считаться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5434</Index>
			<Text>Большая регенерирующая бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5435</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня может выдержать приличное количество повреждений.И оснащена нано-ремонтными ботами, которые выпускаются, когда корабль начинает получать повреждения, исцеляя каждый модуль на корабле. Эффекты экипированных модулей брони сумируються, и корабль, оснащенный регенерирующей броней, - это сила, с которой нужно считаться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5436</Index>
			<Text>Плазменная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5437</Index>
			<Text>Эту плазменную пушку лучше всего устанавливать на фрегаты. Она выпускает поток плазменных снарядов по ничего не подозревающим целям.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5438</Index>
			<Text>Реактор Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5439</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелая пушка Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5440</Index>
			<Text>Двигатель титана Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5441</Index>
			<Text>ЭМИ бластер Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5442</Index>
			<Text>Бластер Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5443</Index>
			<Text>Передний ускоритель I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5444</Index>
			<Text>Это небольшое переднее подруливающее устройство, устанавливаеться снаружи корабля, а не в обычном выделенном машинном отделении. Экономически выгодно, когда требуется большая скорость.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5445</Index>
			<Text>Передний ускоритель II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5446</Index>
			<Text>Это переднее подруливающее устройство немного большего размера, устанавливаеться снаружи корабля, а не в обычном выделенном машинном отсеке. Экономически выгодно, когда требуется большая скорость.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5447</Index>
			<Text>Передний ускоритель III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5448</Index>
			<Text>Это большое переднее подруливающее устройство, используещее силы анти-материи, устанавливаеться снаружи корабля, а не в обычном выделенном двигательном отсеке. Экономически выгодно, когда требуется большая скорость.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5449</Index>
			<Text>Передний ускоритель IV</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5450</Index>
			<Text>Это очень большое переднее подруливающее устройство, используещее силы анти-материи, устанавливаеться снаружи корабля, а не в обычном выделенном двигательном отсеке. Экономически выгодно, когда требуется большая скорость.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5451</Index>
			<Text>Малый прыжковый двигатель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5452</Index>
			<Text>Это специализированный варп-двигатель используещий силы анти-материи. Большинство из них можно установить внутри корабля для большей защиты. Он не обеспечивает ни тяги, ни тяги при повороте.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5453</Index>
			<Text>Средний прыжковый двигатель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5454</Index>
			<Text>Это специализированный варп-двигатель используещий силы анти-материи. Большинство из них можно установить внутри корабля для большей защиты. Он не обеспечивает ни тяги, ни тяги при повороте.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5455</Index>
			<Text>Большой прыжковый двигатель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5456</Index>
			<Text>Это специализированный варп-двигатель используещий силы анти-материи. Большинство из них можно установить внутри корабля для большей защиты. Он не обеспечивает ни тяги, ни тяги при повороте.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5457</Index>
			<Text>Скоростной пакет I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5458</Index>
			<Text>Скоростной пакет II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5459</Index>
			<Text>Скоростной пакет III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5460</Index>
			<Text>Скоростной пакет IV</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5461</Index>
			<Text>Скоростной пакет V</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5462</Index>
			<Text>По мере того как наш контроль над галактикой растет, мы должны улучшать время путешествия в гиперпространстве и подпространстве. Мы делаем упор на внешние двигатели и более интегрированные системы для истребителей / корветов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5463</Index>
			<Text>Зеленый лазер Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5464</Index>
			<Text>Технологии Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5465</Index>
			<Text>Планетарная ядерное оружие Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5466</Index>
			<Text>Эксперементальная установка"Врата"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5467</Index>
			<Text>У экспериментальных ворот есть активные прототипы звездных карт, которые могут отправлять ваши войска на дальние миссии. Изучение новых миров и цивилизаций может принести с собой новые технологии, богатство за пределами вашего воображения, или невероятно опасные и потенциально смертельные встречи.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5468</Index>
			<Text>Может открыть двусторонние врата в далекие миры и галактики.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5469</Index>
			<Text>Орудие магнитного ускорения</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5470</Index>
			<Text>Орудие магнитного ускорения- чрезвычайно мощное оружие, способное уничтожать небольшие суда одним выстрелом, независимо от того, есть у них щиты или нет. Также обладает высокой способностью к пробитию брони.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5471</Index>
			<Text>Средний грузовой отсек с элементарными возможностями жизнеобеспечения. В этом трюме может храниться 9 единиц еды, или продукции,а также небольшое количество колонистов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5472</Index>
			<Text>Средний грузовой отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5473</Index>
			<Text>Орудие магнитного ускорения Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5474</Index>
			<Text>Регенерирующая броня Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5475</Index>
			<Text>Орудие магнитного ускорения Предтечь 2x2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5476</Index>
			<Text>Боевой двигатель Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5477</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный проектор Предтечь</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5478</Index>
			<Text>Синий лазер Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5479</Index>
			<Text>Первое поколение скорострельных лазеров, предназначенных для истребителей. В основном это первый рабочий прототип этого типа энергетического оружия. Его главный минус - большая задержка между очередями, необходимая для охлаждения оружия.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5480</Index>
			<Text>Синий лазер Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5481</Index>
			<Text>Улучшенная версия Mk1. Благодаря большему размеру радиаторов, он может поддерживать быстрый огонь в течение более длительных периодов времени, увеличивая количество выпущенных снарядов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5482</Index>
			<Text>Синий лазер Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5483</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутый скорострельный лазер, который может поместиться в корпус истребителя. Благодаря более лучшему магнитному стволу рельсового типа, снаряды можно запускать с большего расстояния, а каждый выстрел имеет увеличенный запас энергии для большего разрушительного воздействия при ударе.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5484</Index>
			<Text>Зеленая тяжелая лазерная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5485</Index>
			<Text>Зеленая версия стандартной тяжелой лазерной пушки. Она была изменена, чтобы иметь более высокий урон за выстрел, но также и более низкую скорострельность. Немного больше наносит урона щитам.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5486</Index>
			<Text>Пурпурная тяжелая лазерная пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5487</Index>
			<Text>Фиолетовая версия стандартной тяжелой лазерной пушки.Она была изменена, чтобы иметь более низкий урон за выстрел, но более высокую скорость стрельбы. Имеет очень маленький шанс полностью обойти щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5488</Index>
			<Text>Ракетный терминал I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5489</Index>
			<Text>Эти ракеты используют дополнительную скорость за счет наведения.Имеют финальную фазу, чтобы преодолеть системы противоракетной защиты. Мы можем создать ракету средней дальности, которая будет использовать эту технологию.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5490</Index>
			<Text>MIRV I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5491</Index>
			<Text> Многочисленные независимые ракетные компоненты. Термин взят из старых планетарных баллистических ракет. Мы можем создать ракету большой дальности (LRM), которая будет содержать несколько ракет, запускаемых рядом с целью, чтобы заполнить зону боя меньшими ракетами и избежать системы точечной защиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- all new armor med and large description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>5999</Index>
			<Text>Это увеличенная версия маленького модуля. Он также более эффективен и обычно более рентабелен, чем несколько модулей меньшего размера, установленных вместо одного модуля большего размера. См. Описание маленького модуля для деталей.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- XX01 -->
		<Token>
			<Index>6501</Index>
			<Text>ракеты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6502</Index>
			<Text>ракеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6503</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная капсула</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6504</Index>
			<Text>Ракетная капсула</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6505</Index>
			<Text>Двойные управляемые ракеты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6506</Index>
			<Text>Двойные управляемые ракеты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6507</Index>
			<Text>Защита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6508</Index>
			<Text>Эта ветка исследований сосредоточена на средствах защиты наших кораблей и колоний от вражеского огня. У нас есть несколько областей, в которых мы можем начать исследования.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6509</Index>
			<Text>Электроника и защита щитов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6510</Index>
			<Text>Электроника и защита щитов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6511</Index>
			<Text>Реакторы и щиты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6512</Index>
			<Text>Реакторы и щиты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6513</Index>
			<Text>Склад</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6514</Index>
			<Text>Склад</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6515</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный торпедный отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6516</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный торпедный отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6517</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный торпедный отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6518</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелобронированная пусковая установка торпедных аппаратов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6519</Index>
			<Text>Тактическое ядерное оружие</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6520</Index>
			<Text>Тактическое ядерное оружие, или не стратегическое ядерное оружие - это ядерное оружие, которое предназначено для использования на поле боя, в основном с дружественными силами в непосредственной близости. Ядерные эффекты, адаптированные для использования в космосе, менее сильны, чем атмосферные взрывы, но все же часто вызывают повреждение ЭМИ.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6521</Index>
			<Text>Тактическая ядерная ракета</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6522</Index>
			<Text>Ядерная тактическая ракета. Может вызывать разрушительные эффекты, а также повреждение ЭМИ.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6523</Index>
			<Text>КРБЛ</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6524</Index>
			<Text>КРБЛ</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6525</Index>
			<Text>КРБЛ</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6526</Index>
			<Text>Корабельные ракеты борьбы с линкорами, намного более мощные, чем обычные ракеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6527</Index>
			<Text>Двойные КРБЛ</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6528</Index>
			<Text>Двойные КРБЛ. Мы также улучшили сами ракеты, добавив немного увеличенную дальность и урон.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6529</Index>
			<Text>Двойные КРБЛ</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6530</Index>
			<Text>Двойные КРБЛ. Мы также улучшили сами ракеты, добавив немного увеличенную дальность и урон.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6531</Index>
			<Text>AMX50 "Револьвер"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6532</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальная качающаяся установка для запуска ракет. Очень дорого, но может запускать 6 улучшенных версий КРБЛ одновременно.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6533</Index>
			<Text>AMX50 "Револьвер"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6534</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальная качающаяся установка для запуска ракет. Очень дорого, но может запускать 6 улучшенных версий КРБЛ одновременно.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6535</Index>
			<Text>XTL7 "Оборотень"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6536</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальное оружейный комплекс, предназначенное для торпедных пусковых установок следующего поколения. Хорошо бронированный, но дорогой.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6537</Index>
			<Text>XTL7 "Оборотень"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6538</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальное оружейный комплекс, предназначенное для торпедных пусковых установок следующего поколения. Хорошо бронированный, но дорогой.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6539</Index>
			<Text>Ракеты истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6540</Index>
			<Text>Уменьшенная версия тяжелой ракеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6541</Index>
			<Text>Ракеты истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6542</Index>
			<Text>Уменьшенная версия тяжелой ракеты. Боезапас: 10</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6543</Index>
			<Text>КРЛБ истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6544</Index>
			<Text>Это версия КРБЛ для истребителей. Меньший размер - значит меньшая дальность и урон.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6545</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовые рейдеры</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6546</Index>
			<Text>Увеличение размера ангарного отсека значительно улучшило последовательность перезапуска кораблей, а также позволило хранить корпуса немного большего размера (до 72 слотов).</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6547</Index>
			<Text>Звездные рейдеры</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6548</Index>
			<Text>Эти ангары могут хранить даже большие корабли (до 116 слотов), самое большое преимущество этих ангаров это - их способность перезапускать корабли намного быстрее после их уничтожения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6549</Index>
			<Text>Ремонтный отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6550</Index>
			<Text>Этот ремонтный отсек, устанавливаемый на большие корабли, значительно увеличит ремонтные возможности корабля. Он также содержит небольшую электростанцию, что делает его полезным в качестве вспомогательного силового проводника.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6551</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний истребительный отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6552</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний истребительный отсек, можно установить внутри корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6553</Index>
			<Text>Внутренние боевые налетчики</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6554</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний отсек боевых налетчиков, можно установить внутри корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6555</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний штурмовой отсек</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6556</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний отсек штурмовых рейдеров, можно установить внутри корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6557</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний отсек звездных рейдеров</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6558</Index>
			<Text>Внутренний отсек звездных рейдеров, можно установить внутри корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6559</Index>
			<Text>Электро-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6560</Index>
			<Text>Это комбинация металлической брони ранней стадии с добавлением солнечных коллекторов. Эти коллекторы, хотя и обеспечивают меньший приток энергии, чем простые и бронированные солнечные панели,а также накапливают небольшое количество энергии внутри. Недостатки - более высокая стоимость и меньшая прочность (даже ниже, чем у внутренних переборок). В качестве бонуса у них есть некоторая устойчивость к лучевому оружию, поскольку коллекторы нуждаются в тепле для обеспечения энергией.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6561</Index>
			<Text>Реактивная броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6562</Index>
			<Text>Это первое улучшение стальной броней. Реактивная броня определенным образом реагирует на наступательные боеприпасы. Она прочнее, чем стальная броня, но стоит дороже.Немного лучше работает против кинетического оружия.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6563</Index>
			<Text>Керамическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6564</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня немного прочнее чем реактивная броня, она меньше весит, но стоит дороже. Ее кинетическое сопротивление улучшено, и есть некоторое сопротивление лучевому оружею. Аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6565</Index>
			<Text>Малая рективная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6566</Index>
			<Text>Прочнее стали и имеет некоторую устойчивость к кинетике</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6567</Index>
			<Text>Средняя реактивная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6568</Index>
			<Text>Большая реактивная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6569</Index>
			<Text>Композитные сплавы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6570</Index>
			<Text>В два раза прочнее стальной брони, немного легче и в 4 раза дороже. Эта броня обеспечивает лучшее сопротивление против кинетики и лучей, а также имеет некоторое сопротивление против энергетических снарядов. Аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6571</Index>
			<Text>Малая композитная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6572</Index>
			<Text>Средняя композитная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6573</Index>
			<Text>Большая композитная бронеплита</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6574</Index>
			<Text>Кристалическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6575</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня очень дорогая в обработке, но почти такая же прочная, как и броня из композитного сплава, при этом весит намного меньше. Она предлагает улучшение кинетического, лучевого и энергетического сопротивления, а также имеет некоторое сопротивление взрывам. Аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони II"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6576</Index>
			<Text>Малая кристалическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6577</Index>
			<Text>Средняя кристалическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6578</Index>
			<Text>Большая кристалическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6579</Index>
			<Text>Керамическая броня нового поколения.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6580</Index>
			<Text>Малая керамическая броня II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6581</Index>
			<Text>Средняя керамическая броня II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6582</Index>
			<Text>Большая керамическая броня II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6583</Index>
			<Text>Бионические сплавы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6584</Index>
			<Text>Бионическая броня восстанавливается при повреждении.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6585</Index>
			<Text>Бионическая броня устанавливается снаружи на кораблях для защиты. Она может восстанавливать себя, ремонтировать корабль и обеспечивать дополнительную поворотную тягу. Потребляет электроэнергию и много весит. Также аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6586</Index>
			<Text>Малая бионическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6587</Index>
			<Text>Средняя бионическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6588</Index>
			<Text>Большая бионическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6589</Index>
			<Text>Сплавы с памятью формы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6590</Index>
			<Text>Хотя этот металл недостаточно прочен, чтобы служить внешней броней, он может заменить внутренние переборки и помочь отремонтировать корабль, когда он не в бою, а также обладает способностями самовосстановления брони бою. У нее высокое энергопотребление, даже если ничего не ремонтировать.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6591</Index>
			<Text>Сплав с памятью формы при повреждении может медленно восстанавливаться.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6592</Index>
			<Text>Малая переборка с памятью формы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6593</Index>
			<Text>Средняя переборка с памятью формы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6594</Index>
			<Text>Большая переборка с памятью формы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6595</Index>
			<Text>Органическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6596</Index>
			<Text>Органическая броня потребляет энергию и создает небольшое количество боеприпасов для корабля, а также добавляет некоторые способности к ремонту корабля и самовосстановлению. Она также способствует защите от ЭМИ и в некоторой степени устойчива к энергетическим снарядам и лучам. Аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6597</Index>
			<Text>Органическая броня не восстанавливается самостоятельно, а вместо этого медленно восстанавливает боеприпасы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6598</Index>
			<Text>Малая органическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6599</Index>
			<Text>Средняя органическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6600</Index>
			<Text>Большая органическая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6601</Index>
			<Text>Органические биопластины</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6602</Index>
			<Text>Комбинируя искусственный органический материал и предыдущую биологическую броню, мы можем создать вещество со всеми характеристиками обоих материалов, а также улучшить ее сопротивление луче.Слегка повышает мощность энергетического оружия.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6603</Index>
			<Text>Результат сочетания бионических и органических пластин. Пластина теперь ремонтирует весь корабль и восстанавливает боеприпасы.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6604</Index>
			<Text>Малая органическая биопластина</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6605</Index>
			<Text>Средняя органическая биопластина</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6606</Index>
			<Text>Большая органическая биопластина</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6607</Index>
			<Text>Бронированная солнечная панель</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6608</Index>
			<Text>Бронированные солнечные панели. Обеспечивает некоторый приток энергии,сложна в производстве. У этой брони есть интересная способность немного усиливать установленные на кораблях щиты. Поскольку броня генерирует энергию, при разрушении она имеет тенденцию давать небольшой взрыв.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6609</Index>
			<Text>Бронированные солнечные панели для космического корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6610</Index>
			<Text>малая електро-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6611</Index>
			<Text>Средняя електро-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6612</Index>
			<Text>Большая електро-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6613</Index>
			<Text>Солнечная броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6614</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня улучшает электро броню несколькими способами. Создает больший приток мощности, обеспечивает большую прочность, дает больше энергии, лучше усиливает установленные щиты и обеспечивает больший радиус мощности. Однако она по-прежнему менее прочна, чем обычная стальная броня. Имеет некоторое сопротивление лучевому оружию, поскольку коллекторам требуется тепло для обеспечения энергией.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6615</Index>
			<Text>Усовершенствованный бронированный солнечный коллектор обеспечивает питание в небольшом радиусе.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6616</Index>
			<Text>Малая солнечная броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6617</Index>
			<Text>Средняя солнечная броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6618</Index>
			<Text>Большая солнечная броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6619</Index>
			<Text>"Волщебная броня"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6620</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня - кульминация лучшей технологии солнечной брони, которую мы можем создать на данный момент. Она прочнее, лучше усиливает щиты и обеспечивает лучший приток энергии и ее накопление. Поскольку броня также генерирует энергию, при разрушении она имеет тенденцию делать небольшой взрыв.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6621</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальная броня генератора щита. Тип экспериментальной брони, с интегрированным небольшим щитом.!ПОТРЕБЛЯЕТ МНОГО ЭНЕРГИИ!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6622</Index>
			<Text>Малая "Волщебная броня"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6623</Index>
			<Text>Средняя "Волщебная броня"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6624</Index>
			<Text>Большая "Волщебная броня"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6625</Index>
			<Text>Щитовая броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6626</Index>
			<Text>Эта броня имеет сильно улучшенную технологию усиления щита. Она прочнее, чем стальная броня, стоит дороже, больше весит и требует мощности. Также аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6627</Index>
			<Text>Серийная версия эксперементальной електронной брони - 5 Fairy (XSGA5). Значительно снижает потребление энергии, а также улучшает накопление энергии, дальность действия и усиление защиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6628</Index>
			<Text>Малый усилитель брони</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6629</Index>
			<Text>Средний усилитель брони</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6630</Index>
			<Text>Большой усилитель брони</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6631</Index>
			<Text>Frontier Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6632</Index>
			<Text>Лучшая щитовая броня, которая может хранить больше энергии, чем предыдущая. Стоимость производства этой брони очень высока, но выгода очевидна. Уязвимость к энергетическим снарядам еще больше снижается с помощью этой технологии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6633</Index>
			<Text>Форт-броня состоит из керамической брони, композитной брони и большого модуля усиления щита. Это делает ее очень прочным и практически самодостаточным. Прочность находится где-то между керамической и композитной броней. Также аннулирует эффект "Пробитие брони I"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6634</Index>
			<Text>Малая форт-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6635</Index>
			<Text>Средняя форт-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6636</Index>
			<Text>Большая форт-броня</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8001</Index>
			<Text>Турель "Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8002</Index>
			<Text>Турель "Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8003</Index>
			<Text>Быстро вращающаяся турель "Гатлинга". Вращающиеся стволы увеличивают количество выстрелов. Она также имеет угол прицеливания 180 градусов. Будет стрелять только по вражеским ракетам</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8004</Index>
			<Text>Турель "Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8005</Index>
			<Text>Двойная турель "Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8006</Index>
			<Text>Двойная "Турель Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8007</Index>
			<Text>Увеличенная турель "Гатлинга" точечной защиты. Высокая скорострельность и угол поражения 360 градусов делают его оптимальным средством защиты от вражеских ракет.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8008</Index>
			<Text>Двойная "Турель Гатлинга"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8009</Index>
			<Text>Зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8010</Index>
			<Text>Зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8011</Index>
			<Text>Зенитные автоматические орудия имеют в два раза большую дальность действия, чем у обычного ТЗ-оружия. Хорошее оружие против ракет и истребителей. Они имеют дугу огня в 180 градусов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8012</Index>
			<Text>Зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8013</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутая зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8014</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутая зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8015</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутая зенитная авто-пушка - это более крупное и мощное скорострельное орудие, способное поражать истребители. Имеют дугу огня в 360 градусов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8016</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутая зенитная авто-пушка</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8017</Index>
			<Text>ЭЗАП-"Великая стена"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8018</Index>
			<Text>ЭЗАП-"Великая стена"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8019</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальная зенитна авто-пушка. Угол прицеливания: 270 градусов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8020</Index>
			<Text>ЭЗАП-"Великая стена"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8021</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 61 AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8022</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие с боеприпасами AP (бронебойными) по умолчанию. + 5% урона по броне, но -15% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва снаряда: средний</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8023</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 61 APFSD</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8024</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие, использующее специальные боеприпасы APFSDS (Хорошо стабилизированных бронебойных снарядов). + 30% шанс пробить щиты. Радиус взрыва снаряда: Нет / Низкий</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8025</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 61 HESH</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8026</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие с использованием специальных боеприпасов HESH (снарядов с высоко-взрывчатой боеголовкой). + 20% урона по броне, но -80% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва снаряда: очень большой</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8027</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 81</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8028</Index>
			<Text>Величайшая штурмовая пушка из когда-либо созданных. Теперь она имеет двойной ствол и стреляет двумя снарядами, которые имеют существенный шанс пробить вражеские щиты. Специальная монтажная рейка позволяет установить это оружие внутри корабля. Составы, используемые в ее боеприпасах, при ударе вызовут взрыв.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8029</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 80</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8030</Index>
			<Text>Очень большая пушка рельсового типа,использующа специальные боеприпасы APFSDS (Хорошо стабилизированных бронебойных снарядов). Ее огромная масса снаряда может игнорировать щиты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8031</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 74</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8032</Index>
			<Text>Тип 74 это-двигатель очень большой массы, которому помогает встроенный миниатюрный варп-двигатель для приведения в движение снаряда. Специальная монтажная рейка позволяет установить это оружие внутри корабля. Она эффективена против брони, но менее эффективена против щитов. Кроме того, соединения, используемые в ее боеприпасах, при ударе вызовут взрыв.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8033</Index>
			<Text>Штрмовая пушка тип 90 AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8034</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие с боеприпасами AP (бронебойными) по умолчанию. + 10% урона по броне, но -15% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва снаряда: средний</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8035</Index>
			<Text>Штурмовая пушка тип 90 APFSDS</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8036</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие, использующее специальные боеприпасы APFSDS (Хорошо стабилизированных бронебойных снарядов). + 50% шанс пробить щиты. Радиус взрыва снаряда: Нет / Низкий</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8037</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type90 HESH</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8038</Index>
			<Text>Пружинное орудие с использованием специальных боеприпасов HESH (снарядов с высоко-взрывчатой боеголовкой). + 40% урона по броне, но -75% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва снаряда: очень большой</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8039</Index>
			<Text>XAC 0-Локи</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8040</Index>
			<Text>Пружинные пушки с боеприпасами AP (бронебойными) по умолчанию. + 15% урона по броне, но -15% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва: средний</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8041</Index>
			<Text>XAC 1-Бегемот</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8042</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальная пушка, использующая специальные боеприпасы APFSDS (Хорошо стабилизированных бронебойных снарядов) . + 50% шанс пробить щиты. Радиус взрыва: Нет / Низкий</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8043</Index>
			<Text>XAC 6-Тор/Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8044</Index>
			<Text>Пружинные пушки с использованием специальных боеприпасов HESH (снарядов с высоко-взрывчатой боеголовкой) . + 40% урона по броне, но -70% урона по щитам. Радиус взрыва: Огромный</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8045</Index>
			<Text>Термоядерный реактор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8046</Index>
			<Text>Немного лучшая версия старого ядерного реактора. При уничтожении он может взорватся,дает больше энергии,и немного прочнее.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8047</Index>
			<Text>Термоядерный реактор с перегрузкой</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8048</Index>
			<Text>Термоядерный реактор с перегрузкой вырабатывает больше энергии, дополняя свои термоядерные возможности другими передовыми технологиями. В результате его масса и стоимость выше, и он очень хрупкий.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8049</Index>
			<Text>Анти-материальный реактор с перегрузкой</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8050</Index>
			<Text>Этот реактор обеспечивает на 150% больше мощности, чем обычный. Однако присущая ему нестабильность делает его опаснимы при повреждении. Имеет небольшой диапазон питания.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8051</Index>
			<Text>Сопряженные квантовые термоядерные реакторы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8052</Index>
			<Text>Защитная камера, содержащая связанную мощность 6 реакторов квантового синтеза. Камера также оборудована небольшим вспомогательным щитом и группой контроля повреждений, что позволяет ей вносить свой вклад в ремонт корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8053</Index>
			<Text>Сопряженные анти-материальные реакторы</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8054</Index>
			<Text>Переоборудованный ангар с 6 реакторами на антиматерии. Ангар оснащен небольшим вспомогательным щитом и командой по устранению повреждений, которая может помочь в ремонте корабля. Однако будьте осторожны, если ангар будет разрушен, произойдет мощный взрыв.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8055</Index>
			<Text>Параллельный реактор черной дыры</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8056</Index>
			<Text>Параллельный реактор черной дыры. 6 подключенных плазменных реакторов. Огромная выходная мощность. Ангар реактора также оборудован небольшим аварийным щитом и аварийной бригадой, что позволяет ему самостоятельно ремонтироваться. Однако учтите, что в случае уничтожения произойдет мощная взрывная волна!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8057</Index>
			<Text>Реактор холодного синтеза</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8058</Index>
			<Text>Реактор холодного синтеза. Очень стабильный, не разрушается. Чтобы достичь этого, нам пришлось снизить его выходную мощность, чтобы получить такую ​​же энергию, как и в наших предыдущих термоядерных реакторах. Добавление закрытой броневой оболочки обеспечивает более безопасный радиус вывода мощности</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8059</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный реактор холодного синтеза</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8060</Index>
			<Text>Пожертвовав небольшим количеством энергии, мы смогли окружить этот реактор холодного синтеза защитными пластинами, значительно увеличив его долговечность и почти полностью сдерживая взрыв в случае обрушения конструкции.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8061</Index>
			<Text>Бронированный анти-материальный реактор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8062</Index>
			<Text>Этот реактор среднего размера, находящийся внутри броневой оболочки.Оболочка будет содержать большую часть повреждений от взрыва реактора в случае его разрушения. К сожалению, из-за конструктивных ограничений невозможно спроектировать более крупные бронированные реакторы на антиматерии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8063</Index>
			<Text>Технология истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8064</Index>
			<Text>VOB Фригатов</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8065</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это массивный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель, предназначенный для установки снаружи корабля. Обеспечивает варп-тягу,субсветовую тягу и небольшую поворотную тягу. Он также имеет встроенный щит для самообороны.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8066</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это мощный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель. Для самозащиты установлен щит с быстрой перезарядкой. Может быть размещен только на внешнем слое корабля. Из-за высокого энергопотребления и встроенных систем этот модуль взрывается при разрушении.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8067</Index>
			<Text>VOB Крейсеров</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8068</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это массивный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель, предназначенный для установки снаружи корабля. Обеспечивает варп-тягу,субсветовую тягу и небольшую поворотную тягу. Он также имеет встроенный щит для самообороны.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8069</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это массивный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель, предназначенный для установки снаружи корабля. Обеспечивает варп-тягу,субсветовую тягу и небольшую поворотную тягу. Он также имеет встроенный щит для самообороны.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8070</Index>
			<Text>Социо-Инженерия</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8071</Index>
			<Text>Ксено шахты II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8072</Index>
			<Text>По мере роста нашей цивилизации мы должны найти способы использовать больше промышленного потенциала наших колоний. Исследования в этой области включают множество шагов в направлении создания прочной промышленной основы, которая будет поддерживать нашу экономику.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8073</Index>
			<Text>Модернизированные ксено шахты</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8074</Index>
			<Text>Эти шахты оснащены более совершенными технологиями для разработки большего количества месторождений полезных ископаемых планеты. Их побочные продукты могут продаваться на местных рынках, принося небольшой доход.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8075</Index>
			<Text>Инвазивная добыча</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8076</Index>
			<Text>Разработка эффективной автоматизации - важный шаг, необходимый для увеличения объемов производства в наших колониях за счет ущерба окружающей среде.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8077</Index>
			<Text>Робототехническая фабрика</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8078</Index>
			<Text>Робототехническая фабрика. Великое технологическое чудо. Эти заводы используют роботов для производства и полностью автоматизированы. Эти фабрики эксплуатируют полезные ископаемые, не зависящие от минерального богатства планеты, но это происходит за счет серьезной нагрузки на окружающую среду планеты.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8079</Index>
			<Text> (-0.5) плодородия за постройку, +6 продукции за ход, +1 еды за ход, +15% налоговой доходности, +100 места на складе, +1 к инфраструтуре.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8080</Index>
			<Text>Нано шахта</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8081</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутые наноботы автоматически распространяются под землей, вынося минералы на поверхность. Это имеет небольшое влияние на окружающую среду планеты, поэтому рекомендуется соблюдать осторожность перед строительством.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8082</Index>
			<Text> (-0.2) плодородия за постройку, +4 к продукции за богатство</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8083</Index>
			<Text>Промышленность III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8084</Index>
			<Text>Это исследование сделает производственные процессы почти полностью автоматизированными и сделает каждую колонию основным производственным центром.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8085</Index>
			<Text>Нано асамблея</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8086</Index>
			<Text>Практически самодостаточный обновленный вариант фабрики роботов. Его воздействие на окружающую среду снижено, способствует развитию исследовательской отрасли, а также освобождает время для колонистов, которое они могут провести дома, увеличивая доход как потребители.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8087</Index>
			<Text> (-0.2) плодородия за постройку, +5 продукции за ход , +0.25 исследований за ход, +10% налоговой доходности, +2 к инфраструктуре.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8091</Index>
			<Text>Ксенофермерство II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8092</Index>
			<Text>Чтобы оставаться счастливыми и полезными, у наших колонистов должно быть достаточно еды на столах. Мы должны инвестировать в более эффективные методы ведения сельского хозяйства, чтобы увеличить производство продуктов питания в каждой колонии.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8093</Index>
			<Text>Улучшенная ксено ферма</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8094</Index>
			<Text>Модернизированные ксено фермы, используют еще более совершенные методы земледелия на чужеродной почве.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8095</Index>
			<Text>VOB Линкора</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8096</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это массивный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель, предназначенный для установки снаружи корабля. Обеспечивает варп-тягу,субсветовую тягу и небольшую поворотную тягу. Он также имеет встроенный щит для самообороны.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8097</Index>
			<Text>VOB Титана</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8098</Index>
			<Text>VOB - это массивный вспомогательный высокоскоростной усилитель, предназначенный для установки снаружи корабля. Обеспечивает варп-тягу,субсветовую тягу и небольшую поворотную тягу. Он также имеет встроенный щит для самообороны.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8099</Index>
			<Text>Авто-турель тип 54</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8100</Index>
			<Text>Это базовая двухствольная автоматическая турель, предназначенная для работы в вакууме. Ее главное преимущество заключается в том, что она может быть установлена на небольших судах.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8101</Index>
			<Text>Авто-турель тип 62</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8102</Index>
			<Text>Автоматическая турель среднего размера. 3 ствола, средней и большой дальности,тяжелые снаряды. Они хорошо работают при установке в группе.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8103</Index>
			<Text>Авто-турель тип 80</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8104</Index>
			<Text>Самая тяжелая турель, которая практически может быть установлена ​​на космические корабли. Имеет четыре ствола и защиту.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8105</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота фригата</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8106</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота - это небольшие устройства, установленные на борту корабля. Они могут значительно увеличить скорость поворота корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8107</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота крейсера</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8108</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота - это небольшие устройства, установленные на борту корабля. Они могут значительно увеличить скорость поворота корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8109</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота линкора </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8110</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота - это небольшие устройства, установленные на борту корабля. Они могут значительно увеличить скорость поворота корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8111</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота титана</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8112</Index>
			<Text>Усилитель поворота - это небольшие устройства, установленные на борту корабля. Они могут значительно увеличить скорость поворота корабля.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8113</Index>
			<Text>XGC-ForAnswer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8114</Index>
			<Text>406-мм пушка Гатлинга "ForAnswer (XGC-63)" выводит термин "количество важнее качества" на совершенно новый уровень и быстро превратит любой корабль, в непригодный для переработки мусор! Она также поедает боеприпасы, как будто они выходят из моды.Лучше всего использовать против больших кораблей.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8115</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутые энергопушки</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8116</Index>
			<Text>Продвинутые энергопушки</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8117</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8118</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный дробовик, подходящее орудие для ближнего боя.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8119</Index>
			<Text>Двойной плазменный дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8120</Index>
			<Text>Двойной плазменный дробовик,отличное оружие ближнего боя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8121</Index>
			<Text>Ионный дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8122</Index>
			<Text>Ионный дробовик ,подходящее орудие для ближнего боя.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8123</Index>
			<Text>Тройной ионный дробовик</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8124</Index>
			<Text>Тройной ионный дробовик ,отличное орудие для ближнего боя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8125</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Пустота"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8126</Index>
			<Text>Дробовик "Пустота", подходящее орудие для ближнего боя.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8127</Index>
			<Text>XAVSG-"Расколотые небеса"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8128</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальный дробовик(XAVSG-"Расколотые небеса") требует огромной мощности для стрельбы. Однако генераторы щита едва выдерживают выстрел.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8129</Index>
			<Text>Генератор Истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8130</Index>
			<Text>Это усовершенствованный генератор истребителей, работающий на термоядерном синтезе, в сочетании с некоторыми новыми технологиями холодного синтеза. Его легче охладить в рамах истребителя или корвета, поэтому он недоступен для корпусов большего размера.По-прежнему очень нестабилен при повреждениях.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8131</Index>
			<Text>"VOB"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8132</Index>
			<Text>VOB обеспечивает высокую мощность варпа в сочетании с небольшим щитом. Благодаря высокой потребляемой мощности и встроенным системам может быть установлен на наших фрегатах и ​​небольших судах.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8133</Index>
			<Text>ASG турель истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8134</Index>
			<Text>Использование Вулкан-пушек для стрельбы устаревает, нам нужны более совершенные альтернативы с более широкими огневыми дугами, если мы хотим, чтобы бойцы действительно участвовали в боях.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8135</Index>
			<Text>HASG турель истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8136</Index>
			<Text>Мы можем улучшить наши истребительные турели, добавив превосходную огневую мощь. Это требует более эффективных механизмов вакуумного заряжания боеприпасов.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8137</Index>
			<Text>QF 17-pdr</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8138</Index>
			<Text> QF 17-prd - это 76,2-мм противокорабельная пушка, которая обеспечивает нашим истребителям полезные возможности.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8139</Index>
			<Text>Проектор расплавления</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8140</Index>
			<Text>Проектор расплавления</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8141</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8142</Index>
			<Text>Плазменный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8143</Index>
			<Text>Ионный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8144</Index>
			<Text>Ионный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8145</Index>
			<Text>Антиматериальный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8146</Index>
			<Text>Антиматериальный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8147</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелый Антиматериальный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8148</Index>
			<Text>Тяжелый Антиматериальный проектор</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8149</Index>
			<Text>ЭПП-"Алый дождь"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8150</Index>
			<Text>Экспериментальный проектор пустоты "Алый дождь". Как и следует из названия, он обстреливает цели,до тех пор, пока они не будут полностью уничтожены.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8151</Index>
			<Text>Торпеда истребителя</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8152</Index>
			<Text>Оружие класса "Торпеда", установленное на истребителях. Из-за своего меньшего размера оно имеет сравнительно меньший урон и дальность действия, чем торпеды крупных кораблей, но его полезность все же очевидна.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8153</Index>
			<Text>Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8154</Index>
			<Text>Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8155</Index>
			<Text>Light Torpedoes</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8156</Index>
			<Text>Light Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8157</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8158</Index>
			<Text>As our ships grow larger, so too do their munition requirements. We can invest research into more efficient, larger storage modules for our ammunition, allowing for more sustainable firepower.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8159</Index>
			<Text>High Capacity Ammunition Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8160</Index>
			<Text>This facility stores ammunition more efficiently than smaller ammunition storages.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8161</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Fabricator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8162</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Fabricator,ammo regen:5</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8163</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Assembly</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8164</Index>
			<Text>This facility is a dedicated ordnance manufacturing module. Our larger ships will surely benefit from it during drawn out battles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8165</Index>
			<Text>Nano Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8166</Index>
			<Text>With the invention of nanobots, we now have a way to improve all of our storage techniques. These little robots will sort, transport, and assemble any kind of weapon or ammunition required. They will also allow us to construct an efficient Nano Storage structure on our colonies, able to store and sort massive amounts of food and production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8167</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Colony Module</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>8168</Index>
			<Text>This Colony upgrade module will provide a newly founded colony an additional 20 food and production. Very important in the early stages of any colony. It can also load more colonists than the standard Colony Module.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8169</Index>
			<Text>Automated Ammunition Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8170</Index>
			<Text>This Almost fully automated ammunition storage facility is designed for our capital class ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8171</Index>
			<Text>Battle Cruiser</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8172</Index>
			<Text>A Battle Cruiser is an alternative Cruiser design allowing for more weaponry classes to fit within.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8173</Index>
			<Text>Military Base</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8174</Index>
			<Text>Military Bases are another step forward in colony ground defense. This building allows you to train infantry-class troops at your colony just as with Military Outposts, but they are sturdier and pack more of a punch when holding off ground invasions.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8175</Index>
			<Text>Missile Defense III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8176</Index>
			<Text>It would be wise to improve our planetary defenses with weapons that can deter invaders. A series of giant SAM launchers could be a good start.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8177</Index>
			<Text>Planet Fortification</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8178</Index>
			<Text>A fortified area on the planet with trenches, defense emplacements, and planetary shielding generators.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8179</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Defense Platform</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8180</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Defense Platform</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8181</Index>
			<Text>Military Fortress</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8182</Index>
			<Text>Military Fortress "Ikaragu"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8183</Index>
			<Text>Fortress Cruiser Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8184</Index>
			<Text>Fortress Cruiser Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8185</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Plasma Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8186</Index>
			<Text>We can install internal Plasma bomb bays on our Bombers, capable of inflicting heavy damage to enemy ships, especially versus Armor. The number of bombs per module is limited.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8187</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Ion Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8188</Index>
			<Text>We can develop Internal Ion bomb bays on our Bombers. They would be slightly more effective against shields, while also inflicting EMP damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8189</Index>
			<Text>Strike Bomber</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8190</Index>
			<Text>Strike Bomber, "SouRai"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8191</Index>
			<Text>Assault Battleship</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8192</Index>
			<Text>This massive ship would be great for assaulting planets or breaking through defensive lines. However, it is extremely heavy, thus making it susceptible to flanking.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8193</Index>
			<Text>Assault Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8194</Index>
			<Text>Assault Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8195</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Farming III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8196</Index>
			<Text>We can perfect our farming methods on alien planets in such a way that we will significantly improve our planetary environments, making our colonies flourish. Another step towards truly planet-wide terraforming.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8197</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Xeno Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8198</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Xeno Farms expand upon the Upgraded Xeno Farm technology, enabling the construction of massive farms that produce more food, some without sentient intervention.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8199</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8200</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8201</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8202</Index>
			<Text>Very strong, resistant to Energy Projectiles and Beam. Creates ordnance, turn thrust, has EMP protection, self regenerates, and repairs the ship. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8203</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Med</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8204</Index>
			<Text>repair:120, ammo gen:0.75, EMP res:4500</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8205</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8206</Index>
			<Text>repair:210, ammo gen:1.2, EMP res:9800</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8207</Index>
			<Text>Small Torpedo Tube</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8208</Index>
			<Text>This torpedo tube launches slow-moving but devastating torpedoes, packed to the hilt with explosives. They require substantial ordnance to fire and can be intercepted by point defense weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8209</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8210</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Shield Amplification Armor. Provides more Shield Amplification. The Crystals in this armor are processed and designed to "Streamline" hyper space travel, boosting Warp speed. It also stores abit more power. Cost is high. Energy Cannon vulnerability is minimized.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8211</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8212</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active Armor is a thorough blend of all our knowledge in Solid State Armor Technology. The mass is slightly higher than the already very light Crystal armor, but it fares well against most known damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8213</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8214</Index>
			<Text>Streamlined for hyper space, powerful shield Amplification module, and the toughest underlying armor in this series of technology. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8215</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8216</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8217</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8218</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8219</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8220</Index>
			<Text>A blend of all Solid Armor plates. It reacts with most attack types and reduces their damage. It offers improvments in Resistance over all armor of lower tiers. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8221</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8222</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8223</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8224</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8225</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedo II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8226</Index>
			<Text>An improved version of the previous Fighter Torpedo. Slightly more damage, and faster.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8227</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Anti Matter Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8228</Index>
			<Text>Anti Matter bomb bays can inflict heavy damage upon enemy capital ships. The bombs are powerful, but have no special abilities beyond their pure destructiveness.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8229</Index>
			<Text>Phased Rapid Energy Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8230</Index>
			<Text>This deadly turret has a medium to long range, and can fire rapid high energy projectiles which will bypass shields half of the times. It will also deal increased damage to armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8231</Index>
			<Text>Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8232</Index>
			<Text>Representatives within The Energy Research branch believe they can now use current energy military knowledge to construct fast-tracking Energy Point Defense weapons, useful for intercepting incoming anti-ship enemy missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8233</Index>
			<Text> Advanced Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8234</Index>
			<Text>We can now create Point Defense "Laser" projectiles that will pack more punch against incoming missiles, while retaining the same projectile speed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8235</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8236</Index>
			<Text>An improved version of our kinetic platform cannons, now featuring even higher range, faster projectiles, and more damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8237</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8238</Index>
			<Text>Our most advanced orbital platform weapon yet. With the extreme range, fast projectile speed, and long reload times, some have come to calling them orbital sniper cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8239</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8240</Index>
			<Text>A high performance twin Kinetic Cannon, specially designed for small and heavy platforms in high orbit around a planet. It features a high range, and the 360 degree swivel allows for the maximum field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8241</Index>
			<Text>Small Sensor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8242</Index>
			<Text>Information in war is most crucial, with that mindset long range sensors were developed. Equiping a ship with a sensor module increases its detection range significantly.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Overdrive -->
		<Token>
			<Index>10003</Index>
			<Text>Automatic Factory</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10004</Index>
			<Text>The Automated Factory is a marvel of engineering, working almost completely without sentient intervention, and remaining environmentally friendly.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10005</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Customs Station</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10006</Index>
			<Text>The planetary customs station maintains a small fleet of vessels that board and inspect all ships moving throughout the system. This ensures that all customs and taxes are paid. It also adds some storage space.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10007</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Network Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10008</Index>
			<Text>The GalNet is a computer network spanning your entire empire, using specialized satellites and passing ships to carry information across the vast gulfs between the stars. Not only does it give access to staggering amounts of silly animal pictures, it also improves research and commerce on any planet connected to it.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10009</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Stock Exchange</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10010</Index>
			<Text>The Galactic Stock Exchange is the central place where stocks of galactic mega-corporations are traded. The proceeds can be taxed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10011</Index>
			<Text>Geo Survey Satellite Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10012</Index>
			<Text>The Geo Survey Satellite Network measures changes in the density of the planet's crust, allowing for the easy detection of all major ore veins. It is mostly suited and cost effective for planets with high richness.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10013</Index>
			<Text>Hive City</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10014</Index>
			<Text>This incredibly massive, highly advanced structure will provide room for 2 Billion population. Due to the extreme amount of land and resources required for construction, planetary fertility will be moderately reduced.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10015</Index>
			<Text>Livestock Cloning Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10016</Index>
			<Text>Instead of the common breeding programs of the past, this building clones meat from various races of xeno livestock, taking advantage of the best genetic attributes. It produces less food than Xeno Farms, but maintenance is very low. Thanks to healthier meat, more ethical lifestyles, and more land available for crops, population growth slightly increases.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10017</Index>
			<Text>Luxury Resort</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10018</Index>
			<Text>A luxurious resort for the very-well-off. Provides a significant boost to planetary commerce without maintenance costs.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10019</Index>
			<Text>Particle Accelerator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10020</Index>
			<Text>A particle accelerator, as the name implies, accelerates particles to nearly the speed of light, smashing them together at relativistic speeds to find new information about the makeup of the universe. Rumors of the potential for an irreversible black hole consumption event caused by this device are likely greatly exaggerated.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10021</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Stock Exchange</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10022</Index>
			<Text>The Planetary Stock exchange allows stocks of planetary companies to be traded. This improves commerce on the planet and thus tax revenue.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10023</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Supercomputer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10024</Index>
			<Text>While advances in miniaturization have made computers smaller, they may inversely allow computers to be scaled up almost indefinitely. Set into the planetary crust, this gigantic computer can crunch almost unimaginable amounts of data, helping scientists immensely.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10025</Index>
			<Text>Plant Genetic Manipulation Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10026</Index>
			<Text>This building adapts local and foreign flora to grow better within a planet's individual climates, promoting greater yields. Thus, larger areas of the planet can sustain agriculture, in effect improving the fertility level.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10027</Index>
			<Text>Soil Enrichment Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10028</Index>
			<Text>In an attempt to improve agricultural output, the planet's soil is enriched to support plant growth, increasing fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10031</Index>
			<Text>System Research Network Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10032</Index>
			<Text>The System Research Network links all research labs, universities and test centers in a system together, allowing scientists to communicate and cooperate easily, limited only by the speed of light.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10033</Index>
			<Text>Weather Manipulation Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10034</Index>
			<Text>Using advanced computers and a network of specialized satellites, this buildings monitors the global weather and directs measures to manipulate it to improve plant growth. This increases the average fertility of the planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10035</Index>
			<Text>Zero Gravity Production Plant</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10036</Index>
			<Text>Certain advanced alloys cannot be produced under conditions of gravity. Orbital production plants allow fabrication in zero gravity, increasing productivity.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10037</Index>
			<Text>Livestock Cloning</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10038</Index>
			<Text>Rather than raising whole animals for meat, this facility will grant us the ability to efficiently clone edible meat to exact specifications, eliminating the need for slaughterhouses and freeing up vast tracks of land. This will improve the food supply of the colony and promote a growing population.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10039</Index>
			<Text>Hive Cities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10040</Index>
			<Text>Specifically designed to house as many people as possible, Hive Cities rise high above the planet's surface, providing housing for 4 billion people. Each home is fitted with advanced holographic emitters and spacial distortion fields, allowing people to comfortably live in an incredibly small area, with as much freedom as they could possibly desire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10041</Index>
			<Text>Soil Enrichment</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10042</Index>
			<Text>Combining artificial and natural fertilizer, we can improve a planet's fertility to increase agricultural output.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10043</Index>
			<Text>Plant Genetic Manipulation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10044</Index>
			<Text>By manipulating local and alien plants, we can adapt them to the environment to grow better and yield more. In effect, this increases a planet's fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10045</Index>
			<Text>Weather Manipulation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10046</Index>
			<Text>By manipulating a planet's climate, we can decrease devastating weather effects while preserving the optimal conditions for plant growth. In effect, this increases a planet's fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10047</Index>
			<Text>Geo Survey</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10048</Index>
			<Text>We can create a network of satellites that will help discover new ore veins, whereas with conventional detection methods they would ordinarily be overlooked.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10049</Index>
			<Text>Zero Gravity Production</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10050</Index>
			<Text>Certain advanced alloys can only be produced in zero gravity. We can now build facilities that exploit microgravity for production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10051</Index>
			<Text>Asteroid Tracking</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10052</Index>
			<Text>Even the star systems without extensive asteroid belts still receive the occasional visitor. With this technology, we can track and mine these passing asteroids.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10053</Index>
			<Text>Automatic Production</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10054</Index>
			<Text>Using advancements in computing and industrial robot design, we can create a factory that produces goods almost completely without intervention.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10055</Index>
			<Text>System Networks</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10056</Index>
			<Text>While linking computers together seems fairly simple on a planet, it is quite a bit more difficult between planets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10057</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Computing</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10058</Index>
			<Text>Using new discoveries in chip design, we can create a supercomputer capable of crunching incredible amounts of data.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10059</Index>
			<Text>Particle Accelerator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10060</Index>
			<Text>The last remaining questions about the origin of the universe can be answered by taking the smallest parts of it and smashing them together.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10061</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Networks</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10062</Index>
			<Text>If connecting planets of a system together was difficult, transferring data between systems will be even harder. With this technology, we can now finally open high data transfer in the GalNet. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10063</Index>
			<Text>Imperial Customs</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10064</Index>
			<Text>Trade between planets must be regulated to protect the local economies, avoid ecological contamination, and, most of all, to ensure that the state get its cut of all proceeds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10065</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Stock Trade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10066</Index>
			<Text>Any planetary government seeking to stimulate economic growth would be well-advised to create a place where companies can find investors. The increase in tax revenue is just a bonus.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10067</Index>
			<Text>Luxury Resorts</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10068</Index>
			<Text>The more planets we explore, the more areas we find that lend themselves well to tourism. Building a resort allows the very wealthy to spend their money in one of these beautiful havens.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10069</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Stock Trade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10070</Index>
			<Text>The level of revenue exchange our galactic mega-corporations require is far beyond the scope of what one planet can accommodate. It would be wise to create a single place in our empire where these corporations can meet with investors. It would be equally wise to tax them for it.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10071</Index>
			<Text>+30% Tax Efficiency, +20 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10072</Index>
			<Text>+1.75 credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10073</Index>
			<Text>+0.1 research per assigned colonist, +0.25 Flat Research, +20% Tax</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10074</Index>
			<Text> (-0.5) Fertility on build, +2 planet population, +100 storage, +2 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10075</Index>
			<Text>+3 Production per Richness, +100 Storage, aids in ship repair, +1 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10076</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 food per assigned colonist, +0.05 population per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10077</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 flat Research, +0.25 research and credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>10078</Index>
			<Text>+2 production per richness</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10079</Index>
			<Text> (+0.3) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10080</Index>
			<Text>(+0.1) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10081</Index>
			<Text> (+0.5) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10082</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 production per assigned colonist, +20 storage, aids in ship repair</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10095</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Vernier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10096</Index>
			<Text>A basic module that allows for the control of a small craft's direction.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10110</Index>
			<Text>Having developed nuclear-thermal engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small craft. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10113</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Nuclear Thermal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10117</Index>
			<Text>Having developed Plasma Torch engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small crafts. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10119</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Plasma Torch</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10123</Index>
			<Text>Having developed Antimatter engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small crafts. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10125</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Antimatter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10165</Index>
			<Text>This power plant works on the principle of nuclear fission. A containment breach will lead to a rapid irradiation of large portions of the surrounding area, which usually means the ship would have to be scuttled.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10166</Index>
			<Text>Massive Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10167</Index>
			<Text>Large Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10177</Index>
			<Text>This power plant works on the principle of matter-antimatter annihilation. Its power output is similar to the Overload Fusion Reactor, but at less cost, and more rigidity. A containment breach will lead to a violent explosion.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10178</Index>
			<Text>Massive Antimatter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10180</Index>
			<Text>Medium Antimatter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10217</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10218</Index>
			<Text>These enormous guns can run the entire length of a frigate, giving even our smaller ships a fairly hefty punch that will threaten ships twice their size.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10219</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10220</Index>
			<Text>This enormous gun runs the entire length of a cruiser, giving any ship featuring it a fairly hefty punch.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10221</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10222</Index>
			<Text>This enormous gun runs the entire length of a battleship. It can deliver a devastating blow to any ship foolish enough to cross before its bow.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10223</Index>
			<Text>Titan Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10224</Index>
			<Text>This gun is the absolute last word regarding any kind of enemy. Larger by itself than many frigates, it can destroy certain ships in only a single hit.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10279</Index>
			<Text>This armor is made up of Liquid Crystals. These are made to flow into any breach and harden in seconds, allowing the armor to repair itself in moments. This gives it unprecedented durability, granting 20% better protection by mass compared to Ceramic Composite Armor. Needs power to function.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10280</Index>
			<Text>Medium Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10281</Index>
			<Text>Small Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10282</Index>
			<Text>Large Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10290</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Sanitation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10291</Index>
			<Text>A planetary Sanitation Center can reduce fatalities from natural diseases, improving lifespans for the colony and also increase maximum population in the colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10292</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 population, +0.01 population growth</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10293</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Education</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10294</Index>
			<Text>Educating future scientists and engineers is the key to our empire's survival. We can research and build Planetary Education Centers to promote and provide ground works for this population.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10295</Index>
			<Text>+0.15 production and +0.15 research per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10296</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Transportation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10297</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Transportaion converts military transportation technologies and methods for civilian usage, which would increase overall efficiency in the colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10298</Index>
			<Text>+0.3 production per colonist, +1 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10325</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10326</Index>
			<Text>A scaled-up version of the Medium Ordnance Storage, this module holds more ammunition and is more cost effective.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10333</Index>
			<Text>Medium Cargo Hold</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10334</Index>
			<Text>Advances in ship design and material science allow for much larger cargo holds to be constructed. This one holds 5 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10335</Index>
			<Text>Large Cargo Hold</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10336</Index>
			<Text>Advances in ship design and material science allow for much larger cargo holds to be constructed. This one holds 15 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10337</Index>
			<Text>Container Deck</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10338</Index>
			<Text>Rather than redesigning the cargo hold, this new approach aims to redesign the cargo. By placing it in standardized, self-sufficient containers, we can maximize the amount of cargo carried. This container deck carries 10 containers for a combined storage of 22 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10344</Index>
			<Text>Imperial University</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10345</Index>
			<Text>Bringing together the best and brightest of our Empire will give huge benefits to research and engineering. In one place, our scientists and engineers can cooperate without the barrier of distance. Only one Imperial University can be built per empire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10346</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 research, +0.1 production per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10551</Index>
			<Text>A clever combination of solar panels and steel frames allows for a system that provides power while simultaneously shielding the modules behind it. Provides 25% less armor strength per mass than conventional steel armor and has to be placed on the outside of the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10552</Index>
			<Text>Medium Armored Solar Panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10553</Index>
			<Text>Small Armored Solar Panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10554</Index>
			<Text>Large Armored Solar panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tsun -->
		<Token>
			<Index>13385</Index>
			<Text>Honor-less Scum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13386</Index>
			<Text>Scum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>3387</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hull Reinforcement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>3388</Index>
			<Text>Using new breakthroughs in hull reinforcement and super structure, the Tsunari have developed this substantially larger freighter.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dauntless -->
		<Token>
			<Index>12001</Index>
			<Text>Steel HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12002</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Steel Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12003</Index>
			<Text>Kinetic Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12004</Index>
			<Text>This general-purpose cannon turret fires kinetic projectiles at high velocity that deal significant damage upon impact. Ideal against armored targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12005</Index>
			<Text>Solar Array</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12006</Index>
			<Text>Solar Panels harvest energy from stars to supplement a ships main power core.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12007</Index>
			<Text>Class I MagShield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12008</Index>
			<Text>Whilst only capable of withstanding a few hits, Magnetic fields are able to cover a wide area and are restored rapidly. This makes them ideal for drawn out skirmishes with smaller ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12009</Index>
			<Text>Medium Overdrive Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12010</Index>
			<Text>This frigate engine has been pushed to the limit, using twice as much power to deliver an additional 50% thrust.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12011</Index>
			<Text>Auxiliary Power Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12012</Index>
			<Text>All-in-one power diagnostics unit. Provides and stores power as well as increasing warp speed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12013</Index>
			<Text>Twin Small Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12014</Index>
			<Text>Coupling multiple engines allows core components to be shared, reducing weight and power usage without a loss to maximum thrust. This does make it easier to disable, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12017</Index>
			<Text>Micro Warp Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12018</Index>
			<Text>This external engine channels energy directly from the central warp core and is able to boost a ships speed a significant amount, at both warp and sublight speeds. Unfortunately, safety standards require that this engine design cannot be used for maneuvering; this is to avoid the unfortunate possibility of the ship tearing itself to pieces.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12019</Index>
			<Text>Solar Plate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12020</Index>
			<Text>Solar Panels harvest energy from stars to supplement a ships main power core. This variant is mounted on a Steel armor Plate to maximize ship defense. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12021</Index>
			<Text>Static Barrier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12022</Index>
			<Text>Placed on the outside of a ship's hull, these units are charged slowly until they form a powerful, albeit highly localized electromagnetic shield.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12023</Index>
			<Text>Jump Drive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12024</Index>
			<Text>Putting recent innovations in warp theory to work, this drive is capable of traversing systems in mere seconds. While its speed puts conventional drives to shame, it is incredibly power hungry and must be recharged in-between jumps. The structural integrity of this module is very unstable. It is advised to protect it with armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12025</Index>
			<Text>Gunships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12026</Index>
			<Text>Gunships are a specialized range of lighter Frigates. They are designed to carry a vast array of weaponry, but are often easily destroyed due to their lack of armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12027</Index>
			<Text>Small Inertial Damper</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12998</Index>
			<Text>This Class V shield is a sturdier improvement of the Class III shields. It also costs more, weighs more, and needs more power to function.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12999</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13000</Index>
			<Text>This is a better armored and more powerful canopy generator. Its power draw is exceptionally high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13001</Index>
			<Text>Canopy Shields II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17402</Index>
			<Text>Gunboat</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17403</Index>
			<Text>BioArmor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17404</Index>
			<Text>Electroplate Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17405</Index>
			<Text>Advanced storage and food preservation techniques allow for massive storage upgrades on our colonies. An extra 500 food and production can be stored in this hi-tech structure's warehouses.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17406</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 research per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17407</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 research per turn, +0.2 production per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17408</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 food per assigned colonist, +50 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17409</Index>
			<Text>+1 food per assigned colonist, +2 Flat Food, +75 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17410</Index>
			<Text> +1 production per assigned colonist,+0.1 Credits per Colonist, +50 storage, +2 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced Missile Armor -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17411</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Missile Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17412</Index>
			<Text>We have perfected a new technology to further increase the survivability of our missile-based weaponry by protecting them with advanced armor plating.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17413</Index>
			<Text>Advanced ECM</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced ECM Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17414</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Electronic Counter Measures can further confuse enemy point defense sensors into missing their targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planet Fortification Building-->
		<Token>
			<Index>17415</Index>
			<Text>We are able to fortify an area on colonized planets which will make ground invasion and orbit bombing harder.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17416</Index>
			<Text>Defensive Building; +1000 Planetary Shields, 2 injuries to each invading troop</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energy pd 2x2 module -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17417</Index>
			<Text>Energy Point Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17418</Index>
			<Text>A Single barreled, energy point defense turret. Created in mind of the constantly growing danger of guided weapons. It has rather low damage, but is accurate and fast firing.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energy pd 3x3 module -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17419</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Energy Point Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17420</Index>
			<Text>An improvement of the basic energy point defense turret. While bigger, it has two barrels, improved rate of fire, and more damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cloud Peak Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17421</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Range Missile Defense</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planetary AutoCannon Emplacement Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17422</Index>
			<Text>Fires auto cannon shells into orbit</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planetary Sniper Cannon Emplacement Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17423</Index>
			<Text>Fires high speed shells into orbit</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Military Base descripsion -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17424</Index>
			<Text>This military facility provides a barracks, armory, mess, firing range, and other facilities needed to train and equip infantry for ground combat. It is more advanced than the military outpost.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- System defense torpedo short descripsion -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17425</Index>
			<Text>Fires long range, very rigid torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Velocity stimulance description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17426</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters, more integrated systems for frigates, and Nuclear Thermal thrusters for improved turn rates.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17427</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for cruisers, new cruiser turn thrusters for improved turn rates, and a new jump drive design.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17428</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for battleships, more advanced jump drives, and a plasma torch thruster.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17429</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for titans, advanced jump theory, and antimatter thrusters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter ASG turrets description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17430</Index>
			<Text>Anti-ship Gatling (ASG) turrets will increase fighter effectiveness in the battlefield. It is essentially a vulcan cannon mounted on a turret for better field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter HASG turrets description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17431</Index>
			<Text>These Heavy Anti-Fighter Gatling turrets use larger ammunition for higher damage. All of this on a better turret with wider field of fire. The projectiles also use the phased defense turret benefits, which can make it very effective vs. Small Craft</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Nano mining tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17432</Index>
			<Text>Using our knowledge in Nano Machinery, we can create Nano Mining Bots. These tiny machines will save a lot of time and effort ordinarily wasted by transporting and drilling in conventional mining operations.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced solar armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17433</Index>
			<Text>Provides power flow, power radius, and power storage within the ship. Not as strong as steel armor, and much more expensive. It also has an improved Shield Amplification technology. Since The armor also generates energy, it tends to yield a small explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Ceramic Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17434</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor can withstand a little more punishment than Reactive Armor, but the true benefit is the decrease in mass. Ceramic Armor is very effective vs. Beams and Energy projectiles, and somewhat effective vs. Energy Projectiles. It is also more expensive than Reactive Armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Composite Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17435</Index>
			<Text>Breakthroughs in Chemistry allow for the design and construction of armors twice as strong as steel, with improvements all arcoss the board.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Crystal Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17436</Index>
			<Text>Purple Crystals are almost as tough as Composite Alloys Armor. We can create armor from these purple crystals, but processing it will be highly expensive. The result would be a very strong armor, with reduced mass, and adding explosion resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced FighterShields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17437</Index>
			<Text>For our fighters to survive in an ever more advanced battlefield, better shields will be needed. We can link two shield generators together, creating an overall stronger shield.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cold Fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17438</Index>
			<Text>Cold fusion is a type of nuclear reaction that would occur at, or near room temperature. This is in contrast with "hot" fusion, which takes place naturally within stars, and under immense pressure.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Shield Armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17439</Index>
			<Text>Breakthroughs in shield amplification lead us to much better amplification in these armors, at the cost of some power draw. We managed to negate some of the previous vulnerability to energy projectiles, but it still remains an issue.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- fairy tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17440</Index>
			<Text>Using knowledge gained from previous Solar Armor, we can reach energy production higher than 50% of Nuclear Reactors within a new armor. The code name given for this project is "Fairy". These also have increased shield amplification.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Assault raiders tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17441</Index>
			<Text>We can construct even bigger hangars to launch faster and bigger corvette size crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Ion Bomb tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17442</Index>
			<Text>This dedicated bomber module launches a barrage of unguided, low accuracy space bombs. The bombs cause EMP damage, and are slightly more effective versus shields, but less effective versus armor. Launches 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Plasma Bomb tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17443</Index>
			<Text>This module launches a barrage of unguided, low accuracy space bombs. The hot plasma is highly effective versus armor. This module fires 4 bomb per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- parallel ion reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17444</Index>
			<Text>Linked Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17445</Index>
			<Text>By repurposing the open space of a hangar bay, we should be able to safely chain together multiple anti-matter reactors, increasing the efficiency of their overall energy output. The hangar might not be very protective, but it's the best our engineers could come up with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Star lancers tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17446</Index>
			<Text>We can construct and maintain very large bays for frigate support.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter generators tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17447</Index>
			<Text>Since fighters offer limited space for systems, our scientists recommend investing research into a high output fusion generator, tailored specifically for fighter skirmishes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17448</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Cold Fusion Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Cold Fusion Reactor. We are also able to upgrade our dedicated power cell's storage due to this advancement.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17449</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Anti-Matter Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Plasma Reactor. We are also able to upgrade our dedicated power cell's storage due to this advancement.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fusion reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17450</Index>
			<Text>In a fusion reactor, the principle is that neutrons generated from Deuterium-Tritium fusion reactions will be absorbed into a blanket containing lithium, which surrounds the core. The lithium is then transformed into tritium (which is used to fuel the reactor) and helium. </Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored shields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17451</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve our Class III shields' output and add Ceramic armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17452</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve our Canopy shields' output and add Ceramic armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter torpedos tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17453</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17454</Index>
			<Text>We can now install Torpedo class weapons on fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17455</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Fighters</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Heavy bomber tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17456</Index>
			<Text>We can develop a new fighter hull type. This fighter will have more internal modules for heavier anti-ship bomb loads.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter high calibers (pdr) tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17457</Index>
			<Text>Fighter High Calibers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17458</Index>
			<Text>We can increase fighter battlefield effectiveness by designing better anti-ship cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- ordnance assembly  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17459</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Facilities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17460</Index>
			<Text>We can design dedicated workshops for ordnance fabrication on capital ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- anti capital missiles  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17461</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Missiles I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17462</Index>
			<Text>We can create missile systems specifically dedicated to destroying enemy capital ships, armed with a warhead capable of efficiently damage armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- dual anti capital missiles  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17463</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Missiles II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17464</Index>
			<Text>We can improve our Anti Capital Ship Missiles by making more powerful warheads at destroying armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighters ATCSM  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17465</Index>
			<Text>We can develop technologies that will allow Anti Capital Ship Missiles to be installed on smaller crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighters Torpedos tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17466</Index>
			<Text>We can develop technologies for smaller torpedoes to be installed on fighter craft.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17467</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17468</Index>
			<Text>Further technological improvements for fighter torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17469</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Gatling defense tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17470</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Defense I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17471</Index>
			<Text>Improving ship Anti-Missile defense systems may limit the loss of life for our ships and crews. We can look into upgrading the previous Phalanx point defense cannons with better radar and more firepower.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17472</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Defense II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17473</Index>
			<Text>With reliable space-based gatling technology finally complete, we should strive for more firepower against the increasing threat of missiles in the battlefield. A larger defense platform will allow us to accomplish this.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Auto Turrets tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17474</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurrets are large, mass driver guns with wide firing angles. They are designed to overwhelm enemy ships with many fast projectiles. Progression in this field involves the design of larger, more powerful turrets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17475</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17476</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17477</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets III</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Flak AA tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17478</Index>
			<Text>Defense Guns I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17479</Index>
			<Text>We can adapt our old air defense weapons for usage in space. These flak turrets will now be capable of targeting fighters, in addition to missiles. Future versions of this weapon will require our engineers to create a larger firing platform.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17480</Index>
			<Text>Defense Guns II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17481</Index>
			<Text>Now that we have a working practice of installing the smaller Flak AA Cannons, our scientists have been able to devise a larger, more powerful platform, perfect for missile and fighter defense on our larger ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Shapemomory armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17482</Index>
			<Text>Advancements in material science now allow us to construct a Shape Memory Metal. This metal will repair itself and other parts of the ship, given enough time. This material also possesses a unique explosive resistance, making it a useful interior bulkhead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Bionic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17483</Index>
			<Text>Bionic alloys can be used to construct a truly unique armor. Slightly stronger than Steel, it can repair the ship, self regenerate, and provide small turn trust through miniature gyroscopic effects in the Bionic Network. It is more expensive than ShapeMemory Alloys, and consumes some power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Organic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17484</Index>
			<Text>We can create an interesting artificial, very hard, but light, organic material. It draws power to maintain functionality, but possesses many special attributes. It is somewhat resistant to energy weapons and beams, thanks to its natural ability to reshape itself. This ability means it can produce ordnance as well. It also has some energy and EMP resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Organic Bioplate armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17485</Index>
			<Text>Combined Organic and Bio Armor. Although less strong than Organic Armor, it has many useful characteristics. It repairs and creates ordnance for the ship, provides turn thrust, self regenerates, and grants EMP protection. The drawback is that it consumes a lot of power. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Adcanved Bionic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17486</Index>
			<Text>This is the most advanced Material we can create in this series of technology. It has all of the Organic Bioplate characteristics, along with some improvements. We have finally turned one of its weaknesses into a strength. Not only is it now much stronger, but its hunger for power is so great, that it has become very resistant to destructive energy beams or projctiles. The cost is very high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- ammo capacity II tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17487</Index>
			<Text>With advancements in AI sorting networks and improved infrastructure, we are able to further perfect the efficiency of our ordnance carrying ship modules. They now support greater ammunition per container than we had ever thought possible, and are mostly automated.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17488</Index>
			<Text>After completely eliminating all manual intervention and maintenance, our ammunition management centers have become completely self contained. By incorporating ammunition drones and robots, the AI seems to utilize advanced logistics needed for the constant flow of ammunition in these very large ship modules. We no longer understand exactly how the AI functions, but it is extremely efficient.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17489</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17490</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity III</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- assault cannons tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17491</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17492</Index>
			<Text>In order to further advance our subspace artillery weapons, we have resorted to the use of new technologies. After extensive testing, our new weapons now feature a miniature warp bubble which has been tied into the driver system, and exotic forms of ultra dense explosive compounds have been synthesized for use as ammunition.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- parallel plasma reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17493</Index>
			<Text>Linked Quantum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17494</Index>
			<Text>By linking the output of our quantum fusion reactors, we can ensure their protection within a small space, and amplify their power output through intuned modulation. They will be protected by their encasing and the addition of a local shielding generator.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Extreme  reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17495</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17496</Index>
			<Text>If we are willing to take the risk, we can construct a higher power flow Fusion Reactor, but at increased mass and cost.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17497</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17498</Index>
			<Text>We are now able to control an advanced magnetic field that can contain multiple, smaller size Anti-Matter reactions. If we are willing to take the risk, we can construct a higher power flow Anti-Matter Reactor that will utilize this newer, more advanced magnetic field. If destroyed, the resulting explosion will be devastating.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored plasma reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17499</Index>
			<Text>Armored Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Hyper Acceleration reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17500</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Acceleration</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17501</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Acceleration can use advanced, massive magnetic coils to accelerate solid projectiles to relativistic speeds, once thought impossible for such amounts of mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- XGC tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17502</Index>
			<Text>Multi Barrel Drivers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17503</Index>
			<Text>We can create heavy, multi barreled cannons, assuming you care more for mass drivers than energy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- advanced fighter shields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17504</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Shields II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- cold fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17505</Index>
			<Text>Cold Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- pulse capacitor small description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17506</Index>
			<Text>Pulse Capacitor - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17507</Index>
			<Text>This is a smaller version of the capacitor, meant for ships with limited space. It is less efficient, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Quantum Fusion Tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17508</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17509</Index>
			<Text>Quantum mechanics concerns the physical phenomena of the smallest scales known. Taking advantage of many tiny changes in quantum energy, this reactor is able to generate power. The variations in energy produced by these reactors is very predictable, making them quite stable. Because of this, they can be built on scales larger than any other reactors thus far.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Quantum Fusion Modules description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17510</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17511</Index>
			<Text>This is a Fighter version of the Quantum Fusion Reactor. It produces less energy than an Anti-Matter Fighter reactor, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17512</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17513</Index>
			<Text>This is the medium version of the Quantum Fusion Reactor. It produces less energy than Anti-Matter medium reactors, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17514</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17515</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor produces less energy than Anti-Matter Fighter reactor, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17516</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor Massive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17517</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor is the biggest single reactor we can build thus far. Its weight and cost is very high. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to Anti-matter technology.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Massive Anti_Matter tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17518</Index>
			<Text>Massive Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17519</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct an incredibly powerful, very large Anti-Matter Reactor. The amount of Anti-Matter stored within is extremely volatile, and should the reactor be destroyed, a powerful explosion will no doubt take place.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored anti-Matter reactor tech name -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17520</Index>
			<Text>Armored Cold Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored quantum Fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17521</Index>
			<Text>Armored Quantum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17522</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Quantum Fusion Reactors in decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Cold Fusion Reactor. We are also able to upgrade our dedicated power cell's storage due to this advancement.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored quantum Fusion reactor description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17523</Index>
			<Text>Armored Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17524</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor has protective armor to contain most of the blast in case of a reactor explosion.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dark-Matter tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17525</Index>
			<Text>Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17526</Index>
			<Text>Although still a mystery to even our greatest minds, this invisible material can be coalesced into small areas. To accomplish this, gigantic, advanced gravitational machines pull ordinary matter apart over vast distances, making way for the dark matter to seep into a proverbial bucket of gravitational potential. By then surrounding and compressing it, usable energy is continuously emitted, making for an incredibly reliable source of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17527</Index>
			<Text>Dark Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17528</Index>
			<Text>This reactor will provide high and stable energy for our ships. Other sizes of Dark Matter reactor are not produced, due the the standardized way the dark matter is collected.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- heavy nuclear bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17529</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Nuclear Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17530</Index>
			<Text>This bomb bay can utilize very powerful Tactical or Strategic Nuclear payloads to bombard enemy colonies. It has a high destructive potential. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- bio terminator bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17531</Index>
			<Text>BioTerminator Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17532</Index>
			<Text>Organic molecules, even those from different worlds, all share many commonalities. By aggressively attacking those common roots, we have created a bomb that will very rapidly and thoroughly kill anything it comes in contact with. A few of these bombs will unquestionably destroy an entire civilian population in short order. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- anti matter bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17533</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17534</Index>
			<Text>This highly destructive bomb turns everything caught in its explosion radius into gamma rays. Very efficient for clearing out enemy colonies. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tritanium Armor Tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17535</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17536</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor is three times stronger than Steel Armor. Though the existence of this material was already previously known, its mass was not yet practical for ships. With our knowledge in Hyper-Active Armor, we can now design low mass Tritanium armor. The cost is very high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17537</Index>
			<Text>The ultimate armor. The strongest material known for its mass/strength ratio. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17538</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17539</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17540</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- mass driver_short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17541</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Short</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17542</Index>
			<Text>This version of the Mass Driver has a shorter barrel, made to fit into smaller ships. Its projectiles have shorter range and less explosion radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17543</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Dual</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17544</Index>
			<Text>Enhanced with attributes of subspace physics, these mass drivers are able to achieve incredible range and power compared to a magnetic mass driver. The dual barrel on this weapon </Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- armored dark matter  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17545</Index>
			<Text>Armored Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17546</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Dark Matter Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Dark Matter Reactor. We are also able to upgrade our dedicated power cell's storage due to this advancement.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17547</Index>
			<Text>Armored Dark Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17548</Index>
			<Text>This Dark Matter Reactor has been enclosed in an armored shell, increasing durability at the cost of slightly less power. In the case of a reactor explosion, damage to nearby parts of the ship will be heavily reduced.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- linked dark matter  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17549</Index>
			<Text>Linked Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17550</Index>
			<Text>Until now, the idea of linking our dark matter reactors to harness more energy has been an impossible one. However, with recent revelations in dark matter theory, we have successfully devised a way to interconnect the spacial inhibitors containing our dark matter, greatly increasing their power efficiency.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17551</Index>
			<Text>Linked Dark Matter Reactor Set</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17552</Index>
			<Text>A state of the art series of 9 Dark Matter Reactors successfully bound together in an advanced protective lab. This facility features a powerful local shielding generator and several small robots that aid in ship repairs.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dark Energy tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17553</Index>
			<Text>Dark Energy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17554</Index>
			<Text>Utilizing an incredibly complex series of warp fields, we can create a localized, massive void of energy, naturally filled in with constant amounts of dark energy. We can then harness this dark energy by collapsing the warp fields, yielding a substantial burst of power. A Dark Energy reactor repeats this process in quick succession, never allowing the dark energy to grow out of hand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17555</Index>
			<Text>Dark Energy Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17556</Index>
			<Text>This Dark Energy Reactor produces vast amounts of energy. We can only construct a large version. Since the process of harnessing dark energy involves the constant inhibition of its expansion, compromising this system will lead to a catastrophic explosion. Energy and Beam weapons will not damage this reactor, however, owing to the energetic voids within.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Missile Point Defense tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17557</Index>
			<Text>Missile PD I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17558</Index>
			<Text>We can adapt our atmospheric missile point defense systems for space usage. It might prove useful for countering enemy missiles at a longer range than mass driver point defense systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17559</Index>
			<Text>Missile Point Defense - Light</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17560</Index>
			<Text>This small turret can launch very fast and agile missiles in a 360 degree field of fire, meant to counter enemy missiles at medium range. The missiles are primed to explode near the targeted enemy missiles, and though their damage is small, the explosive radius is very large. This turret uses a lot of ordnance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17561</Index>
			<Text>Missile PD II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17562</Index>
			<Text>As enemy missiles become more sophisticated, we can compensate by upgrading our Missile Point Defense systems to launch better counter missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17563</Index>
			<Text>Missile Point Defense - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17564</Index>
			<Text>This larger Missile Point Defense turret launches heavier, but still very fast missiles to counter enemy missile attacks at long range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- mass driver_short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17565</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Long</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17566</Index>
			<Text>This version of the Mass Driver has a longer barrel, useful for ships with more space. Its projectiles have longer range and a larger explosive radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- subspace artillery II tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17567</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Artillery II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17568</Index>
			<Text>Using conventional physics, extremely large cannons proved too unwieldy for applications in space. However, advancements in subspace field theory have allowed for the creation of a second set of larger, extremely powerful cannons, along with a tactical one for our more cramped vessels. These weapons will shred through enemy armor, and offer a small to decent chance of penetrating shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17569</Index>
			<Text>Dual Mass Driver - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17570</Index>
			<Text>By increasing the thickness and length of the dual mass driver barrels, this weapon is able to achieve a higher range and damage potential when compared to its smaller counterpart. However, the increased length may make it difficult to fit on our smaller vessels.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17571</Index>
			<Text>Massive Cannon - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17572</Index>
			<Text>Even more monstrous than the massive cannon, only battleships and titans can mount this weapon. It has an even higher chance to penetrate enemy shields, and deals an absurd amount of damage from an incredibly high range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Disintegrator Array II tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17573</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17574</Index>
			<Text>We can now research and construct a larger disintegrator array.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17575</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17576</Index>
			<Text>This is a smaller array for our smaller ships. It does less damage, but requires less power to operate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17577</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array - Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17578</Index>
			<Text>Enemy commanders will quake in fear at the sight of our new large Disintegrator arrays. These hulking weapons can only be fitted on Battleships or Titans, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fast shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17579</Index>
			<Text>Fast Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17580</Index>
			<Text>Since the recharge rate of our Class I Shields is rather low, we can invest research into a slightly stronger medium and small shield with a faster recharge rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17581</Index>
			<Text>Fast Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17582</Index>
			<Text>Since the recharge rate of our Class III Shields is rather low, we can attempt to research a slightly stronger large shield with a faster recharge rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17583</Index>
			<Text>Class I Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17584</Index>
			<Text>This medium shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It is also stronger than a regular class I medium shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power in hyperspace.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17585</Index>
			<Text>Class III Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17586</Index>
			<Text>This large shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It is also stronger than a regular class III large shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power in hyperspace.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Battle shields shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17587</Index>
			<Text>Battle Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17588</Index>
			<Text>We believe it would be possible to further improve our quickly recharging Class I Fast shields by making them a little stronger, and adding the ability to recharge during combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17589</Index>
			<Text>Battle Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17590</Index>
			<Text>We believe it would be possible to further improve our quickly recharging Class III Fast shields by making them a little stronger, and adding the ability to recharge during combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17591</Index>
			<Text>Class I Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17592</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It can also recharge during combat, and it is stronger than a regular Class I Fast shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17593</Index>
			<Text>Class III Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17594</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It can also recharge during combat, and it is stronger than a regular Class III Fast shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17595</Index>
			<Text>Small Stations</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17596</Index>
			<Text>In order to defend our colonies from the growing danger of enemy fleets, we have recently devised blueprints to construct our first orbital station, a new type of structure that is larger than our small and heavy platforms. In addition, the creation of a long-range missile defense system was deemed imperative for our stations, and these weapons should prove effective against any comparatively long range enemy assaults.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Orbital Defense missile tech description -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>17597</Index>
			<Text>Light Orbital Missile Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17598</Index>
			<Text>This fixed-mount missile launcher fires salvos of long range missiles which are effective against a wide range of targets. It is only practical for stations, but can also be installed on our heavy platforms.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- fighter hangars 2 tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17599</Index>
			<Text>Bombers Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17600</Index>
			<Text>These hangars are very similar to standard fighter bays, but they can hold our heavy fighters and bombers, at the expense of longer spawn times.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17601</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Theory II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17602</Index>
			<Text>We can develop a Fighter bay which will be able to hold our larger fighter hulls and our bombers as well.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Anti-Matter bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17603</Index>
			<Text>This is a bomber dedicated Anti-Matter bomb bay. The bombs will inflict heavy, pure damage to slower moving enemy capital ships. This module fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Melt bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17604</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bays</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17605</Index>
			<Text>We can develop internal Melt bomb bays for our Bombers which would be very powerful versus shields, while also causing some EMP damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17606</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bays 3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17607</Index>
			<Text>Melt bombs deal high damage, are effective against shields, and cause some EMP damage. They are slightly more accurate and robust in comparison to other fighter bombs, but they are also slower. This module fires 3 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter shield bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17608</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Shield Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17609</Index>
			<Text>We can develop internal shield-bomb bays for our bombers. These bombs were developed to counter ships that rely on shields as their only means of defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17610</Index>
			<Text>Shield-Bomb Bay 3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17611</Index>
			<Text>Shield Bombs are specifically designed to counter enemies who only use shields to defend their ships. These bombs have a 75% chance to bypass shields and damage ship components, while delivering a small amount of EMP damage. They are not very effective against armor, however. This module fires 3 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17612</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17613</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17614</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Ion Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17615</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17616</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Ion Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17617</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17618</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17619</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17620</Index>
			<Text>Anti Matter Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17621</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17622</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17623</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17624</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Plasma Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17625</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17626</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Plasma Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17627</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17628</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Melt Bomb Bay 3. It fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17629</Index>
			<Text>Shield-Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17630</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Shield-Bomb Bay 3. It fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Blue laser mk4  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17631</Index>
			<Text>Blue Laser Mk4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17632</Index>
			<Text>These are truly high fire rate laser weapons. They also do more damage and require more power to maintain.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		<!-- Nano Storage short description - building -->
			<Index>17633</Index>
			<Text>+600 maximum goods storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Advanced Pulse Capacitor -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17634</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Pulse Capacitor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17635</Index>
			<Text>This is an improvement over the basic electromagnetic capacitor. Any ship equipped with pulse capacitors will be substantially more difficult to disable with electromagnetic pulse weaponry. They also aid the ship to recover faster from EMP overloads</Text>
		</Token>			
		<Token>
			<Index>17636</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Pulse Capacitor - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17637</Index>
			<Text>This is an improvement over the small basic pulse capacitor, meant for ships with tight space. It is less efficient than the bigger version.</Text>
		</Token>	  
		<Token>
			<Index>17638</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Capacitors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17639</Index>
			<Text>Protecting our ships from EMP damage is becoming a necessity. We can design advanced, more efficient versions of our basic pulse capacitors.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- cold shields shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17640</Index>
			<Text>Cold Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17641</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct a very interesting Class I Shield variant. It is now almost fully resistant to Energy beams, accomplished by nullifying their temperature on impact. Hence the term, "Blue Shield". These shields recharge during combat, provide a large protection radius, and consume high amounts of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17642</Index>
			<Text>Cold Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17643</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct a very interesting Class III Shield variant. It is now almost fully resistant to Energy beams, accomplished by nullifying their temperature on impact. Hence the term, "Blue Shield". These shields recharge during combat, provide a large protection radius, and consume high amounts of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17644</Index>
			<Text>Class I Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17645</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a high protection radius and is almost fully resistant to Energy Beams, yet also decently resistant to Energy Projectiles. It recharges during combat, but has a high power demand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17646</Index>
			<Text>Class III Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17647</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a high protection radius and is almost fully resistant to Energy Beams, yet also decently resistant to Energy Projectiles. It recharges during combat, but has a high power demand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Auto Turret type 68 -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17648</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurret Type68</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17649</Index>
			<Text>This 3 barreled turret fires high explosive rounds and an upgrade to the type 62 Auto Turret</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Drone Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17650</Index>
			<Text>Drone AI Command</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17651</Index>
			<Text>Rather than depending on a living being, we can easily design an AI program to take control of a smaller drone fighter. This comes with multiple advantages, such as the elimination of life support systems, as well as greater capacity for acceleration and turning speed. These drones can be launched from a special tube able to be installed on larger ship hulls.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17652</Index>
			<Text>Basic Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17653</Index>
			<Text>This is our first Drone AI command module. It contains the hardware and software of an independent drone, as well as basic power generation and storage.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17654</Index>
			<Text>Improved Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17655</Index>
			<Text>After improving our knowledge in power generation techniques, we are now able to construct an improved command module that can generate and store twice the amount of earlier modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17656</Index>
			<Text>Shielded Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17657</Index>
			<Text>This drone command module as a basic shield installed as well as an improved software, enabling it to track more than one target.</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17658</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Matter Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17659</Index>
			<Text>Drone Plasma Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17660</Index>
			<Text>Drone Ion Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17661</Index>
			<Text>This is a small bomb bay intended for a drone. Typically, it contains only 4 bombs, and the drone will need to resupply at its mothership after two or three bomb runs.</Text>
		</Token>												
		<Token>
			<Index>17662</Index>
			<Text>Drone Pulse Beam</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17663</Index>
			<Text>A pulse beam specifically modified for use on a drone. It is very accurate, but not as strong as its larger counterpart.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17664</Index>
			<Text>Drone Attack Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17665</Index>
			<Text>This attack cannon fires 5 rounds at high velocity in close range bursts. It has limited ammo, usually sufficient enough for a short skirmish.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17666</Index>
			<Text>Basic Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17667</Index>
			<Text>This Basic engine provides thrust and turn thrust for the drone. Drones can withstand much greater G-forces than if a living being were to be present. It is also equipped with a small secondary command unit that can track targets, should the main command module be destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17668</Index>
			<Text>Improved Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17669</Index>
			<Text>This improved engine provides more thrust, as well as some more power storage for the power hungry weapon modules.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17670</Index>
			<Text>Shielded Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17671</Index>
			<Text>This drone engine module provides a little less thrust than the improved engine module, but also comes fitted with a basic shield, providing increased survivability for the drone.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17672</Index>
			<Text>Drone Rocket Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17673</Index>
			<Text>This is a simple rocket launcher that can be fitted on a drone. It has less range than a standard rocket launcher.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17674</Index>
			<Text>Drone Launch Tube</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17675</Index>
			<Text>A tube used to launch a drone into combat. It is cheaper and smaller in comparison to fighter bays, as airlocks are not needed for the drone.</Text>
		</Token>			
		<!-- Nano Ordnance -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17676</Index>
			<Text>Small Nano Ordnance Locker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17677</Index>
			<Text>This Storage locker has been augmented with an army of small Nanobots that assemble the needed type of ammunition from raw materials. Within, ammunition is created in very small parts, allowing this locker to fit 4 times the ordnance of a normal ordnance pod. Drawbacks are higher production cost and a small explosion if the locker is destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>					
		<!-- Plasma vectoring -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17678</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17679</Index>
			<Text>We can accelerate the high-pressure system used to vent plasma from the ship's reactors. This can increase damage output by a high percentage. The density of the plasma will make it slightly more effective versus shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17680</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17681</Index>
			<Text>We can use calibrated reactor power to further narrow the focus of the plasma streams, making the plasma flame more destructive. This comes with a much higher power cost, but it is more effective against shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17682</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring IV</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17683</Index>
			<Text>Using more power and higher pressure systems leads to very focused and lethal plasma vents, at the expense of higher power and ordnance consumption.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17684</Index>
			<Text>High Pressure Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17685</Index>
			<Text>This plasma thrower uses a higher pressure vent system and increases the damage of the plasma cloud. It also fares well against shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17686</Index>
			<Text>Power Assisted Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17687</Index>
			<Text>This plasma thrower vents a more focused plasma cloud thanks to power transfer from the ship's reactors. It is very good versus Shields, but requires high power and more ordnance.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17688</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced Fuel Cells tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17689</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Power Cells</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17690</Index>
			<Text>Advancements into new types battery technology allow us to manufacture higher capacity Power Cells.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17691</Index>
			<Text>Small Advanced Power Cell</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17692</Index>
			<Text>This Small Power Cell can store 50% more power than the basic one and has better, lighter armor than the Small Power Cell.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
			<Index>17693</Index>
			<Text>Medium Advanced Power Cell</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17694</Index>
			<Text>This Medium Power Cell can store 50% more power than the basic one and has better, lighter armor than the Medium Power Cell.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Improved SRMs -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17695</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Fighter Missiles II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17696</Index>
			<Text>We can further improve our short range missile technology by creating more destructive missiles, with additional range and utility.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17697</Index>
			<Text>Lightning Storm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17698</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Shadow Storm, with more missiles per salvo, and increased damage per missile. However, they have a slightly lower chance to penetrate enemy shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17699</Index>
			<Text>Assault Orbital Missile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17700</Index>
			<Text>Likely the longest range weapon ever created, This orbital missile emplacement will launch a barrage of devastatingly powerful and maneuverable missiles, designed to target frigates and larger ships. Missile carriers are launched which propel themselves to the target and separate into multiple fast and evasive rockets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17701</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Orbital Missile Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17702</Index>
			<Text>This orbital missile launcher fires large missiles which are designed to strike frigates and larger ships. It features an extremely long range, and a separation phase when missiles near the target.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Defensive structures description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17703</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Laser Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17704</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Heavy Laser Turret. It can target everything in a short planetary range. Several of these are placed on the planet. Their number (translated to rate of fire) increase as the colony becomes bigger.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17705</Index>
			<Text>Fires Heavy Laser pulses. Short Range.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17706</Index>
			<Text>Disruptor Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17707</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Disruptor Turret. Several of these in key locations have increased damage over the Heavy Laser Turret, but are too imprecise to target Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17708</Index>
			<Text>Fires Heavy Disruptor pulses. Cannot target Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17709</Index>
			<Text>Photon Cannon Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17710</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Photon Turret. Its major advantages are explosive projectiles and longer range. These are placed in multiple location on the planet for maximum coverage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17711</Index>
			<Text>Fires Photon Charges. Medium range. Explosive payload.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17712</Index>
			<Text>System Defense Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17713</Index>
			<Text>This planetary defense emplacement fires guided torpedoes over very long range. The torpedoes are huge and armored, thus physically resistant to point defense. A big colony with these buildings can be devastating to incoming enemy capital ships.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- plasma thrower blue  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17714</Index>
			<Text>Vast amounts of power is used to deliver a lethal plasma cloud which is also excellent versus shields. Sadly, with high power requirements and slightly less range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Extender snipers -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17715</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17716</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17717</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper AP Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17718</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper AP Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>		
				<Token>
			<Index>17719</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper HEAP Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17720</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper HEAP Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Forward shotguns -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17721</Index>
			<Text>Forward H.V.E Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17722</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the H.V.E Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17723</Index>
			<Text>Forward Repeater Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17724</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the Repeater Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17725</Index>
			<Text>Forward E.S Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17726</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the E.S Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17727</Index>
			<Text>Forward Dragons Breath Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17728</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the Dragon Breath Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Rapid laser structures description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17729</Index>
			<Text>Rapid Laser Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17730</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Rapid Laser Cannon. It can target everything in a Medium planetary range and several of these on the planet fire repeating bursts of laser pulses at a high rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17731</Index>
			<Text>Fires Rapid Laser pulses. Medium Range.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Remnant  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17732</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Heavy Laser</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17733</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17734</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Bridge</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17735</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>												
		<!-- some buildings  description -->				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17736</Index>
		  <Text>Pirate Hidden Treasure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17737</Index>
		  <Text>From Orbit, it appears as nothing out of the ordinary. However, your fleet commander insists these are the right coordinates, and ground troops should be sent to investigate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17739</Index>
		  <Text>Friendly natives have been found living on this planet. They are very skilled workers and enjoy bartering for almost any of our trinkets. They offer friendship to the rulers of this planet. +1 production and +1 food per turn to the owner of this planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17740</Index>
		  <Text>+1 production and +1 food per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17741</Index>
		  <Text>Native Village</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17742</Index>
		  <Text>Overdrive Capital Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17743</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced Capital Engines that provide 50% more thrust, but require double the power.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>17744</Index>
		  <Text>Overdrive Titan Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17745</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced Titan Engines that provide 50% more thrust, but require double the power.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<!-- Cockpits description -->				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17746</Index>
		  <Text>Side By Side Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17747</Index>
		  <Text>This Cockpit allows for two pilots to sit side by side, with more integration between systems. It's slightly better than 2 separate cockpits.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>17748</Index>
		  <Text>Tandem Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17749</Index>
		  <Text>This Cockpit allows for two pilots to sit one behind the other, with more integration between systems. It's slightly better than 2 separate cockpits.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- adv fighter shields  description -->						
		<Token>
			<Index>17750</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Shield Generator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17751</Index>
			<Text>A larger module with 2 linked shield generators provides heavy shield support for small craft, probably the best we can ever get. However, the recharge rate is very slow.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- drone cannons improved  description -->								
		<Token>
			<Index>17752</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Fighter Cannon Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17753</Index>
			<Text>This drone cannon has an increased fire rate and a high chance to penetrate shields. It was designed as an anti-fighter weapon, as fighters often depend specifically on shields.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17754</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Fighter Cannon Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17755</Index>
			<Text>This drone cannon is designed to provide more attack force vs. small craft by causing more damage vs. light armor, which some small craft might be equipped with.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17756</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Fighter Cannon Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17757</Index>
			<Text>Improvment of the Mk2 cannon, this Drone cannon is redesigned to deliver exploding shells.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Drone Ion beam  description -->				
		<Token>
			<Index>17758</Index>
			<Text>Drone Ion Pulse Beam</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17759</Index>
			<Text>An Ion pulse beam, specifically modified to fit within a drone. It is very accurate, but not as powerful as its bigger version.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Battle and blue  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17760</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Battle Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17761</Index>
			<Text>In order for our small crafts to survive battles with larger ships, they require better shields. These shields will recharge during combat, but they require more energy to maintain.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17762</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Cold Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17763</Index>
			<Text>With the ability to recharge during combat, along with resistance to beam weaponry, these shields should noticeably improve the battle capabilities of our small crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17764</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17765</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Fast Fighter Shield. It can recharge during combat, but it demands more power.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17766</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17767</Index>
			<Text>This Fighter Shield version is similar to the Fighter Battle Shield, but with high resistance to Energy and Beam weapons as well.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17768</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17769</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Advanced Fighter Fast Shield. It can recharge during combat, but it demands more power.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17770</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17771</Index>
			<Text>This Fighter Shield version is similar to the Advanced Fighter Battle Shield, but with high resistance to Energy and Beam weapons as well.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Xenocide tech  description -->				
		<Token>
			<Index>17772</Index>
			<Text>Biologic Warfare</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17773</Index>
			<Text>Utilizing our knowledge of biospheres and Xeno-Environments, we can design a fearsome biological weapon.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17774</Index>
			<Text>Xenocide</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17775</Index>
			<Text>We can create a deady biological bomb. Assuming we dont mind some... Experimenting. Retaining ethical treatment, we can conduct non life-threatening, temporary trials on test subjects. Be them prisoners of war... Volunteers... Or our own, unsuspecting citizens.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Mega cities and HD housing -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17776</Index>
			<Text>High Density Housing</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17777</Index>
			<Text>Special zones on the planet, specifically designed to house a large amount of the population while maintaining ordinary living standards. Our population will find them more than acceptable to live in.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17778</Index>
			<Text>Mega Cities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17779</Index>
			<Text>Mega Cities are designed to house as much population as is comfortably possible, featuring automated technology to maintain optimal living conditions. It features buildings that rise high into the sky, and bridges interconnecting them. Due to the structure's massive size as well as the resources devoted to construction, large amounts of material must be removed from the surrounding soil, reducing fertility on the planet by a small amount.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17780</Index>
			<Text>This structure was specifically designed to house a large amount of the population while maintaining ordinary living standards. These zones can house 500 Million citizens.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17781</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 planet population, +25 storage, +1 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17782</Index>
			<Text>Mega City</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17783</Index>
			<Text>A Mega City is a zone with high rise skyscrapers, dedicated to housing 1 Billion population in decent living conditions. Due to the loss of vast expanses of arable land, fertility is slightly reduced.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17784</Index>
			<Text> (-0.2) Fertility on build, +1 max population, +50 storage, +1 Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Massive laser and disruptor cannons -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17785</Index>
			<Text>Massive Disruptor Cannon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17786</Index>
			<Text>This is the largest Disruptor cannon we can usefully mount on a spaceship. These Dual cannons can disrupt more efficiently, making them more effective against shields. They also have a better chance to completely penetrate shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17787</Index>
			<Text>Massive Laser Cannon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17788</Index>
			<Text>A bigger version of the Heavy Laser Turret. It can pack quite a punch, increasing its effectiveness versus armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17789</Index>
			<Text>Massive Polaron Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17790</Index>
			<Text>Massive Polaron Cannons mounted on a turret platform with advanced cooling systems for rapid and sustained fire. Bypasses shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- more drone bombs  description -->			
		<Token>
			<Index>17791</Index>
			<Text>Drone Shield Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17792</Index>
			<Text>Drone Cluster Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17793</Index>
			<Text>This is a unique bomb module for drones. It contains 8 miniature fusion bombs designed to strike capital ships. The drone can fire them all in a single bomb run.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- stations -->			
		<Token>
			<Index>17794</Index>
			<Text>Battle Stations</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17795</Index>
			<Text>The need to defend our colonies against enemy invasion grows constantly. Our engineers have designed a substantially large battle station that will bolster the defensive prowess of our more important planets. We have also iterated upon our orbital missile launchers, a step toward nullifying the threat of long range enemy weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17796</Index>
			<Text>Sector Stations</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17797</Index>
			<Text>These hugely massive stations are larger than most titans, and will serve our planets tremendously against almost any threat. Advancements in missile technology have also lead us to an ingenious new orbital missile defense weapon, perfectly suited to combat any large invasion fleet, no matter their range.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17798</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Projectors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17799</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Projectors greatly speed up stardrive speeds for ships within their influence. We can use them as "fast lanes" in our empire. They also have a very large sensor coverage and can be used for spying near enemy borders. Orbital Platforms are also our first step into the colony orbital defense path. These small orbitals, when grouped together, can fend off entire small invasion fleets.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Phased Rapid Energy Cannons -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17800</Index>
			<Text>Gravitons</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		<!-- Massive Photon Turret -->
			<Index>17801</Index>
			<Text>For decades, our scientists have understood and been able to utilize the quantum forces of the graviton particle, in applications such as gravitational plating and warp travel. Now, with our newfound mastery over it, we have been able to devise an incredibly powerful weapon.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17802</Index>
			<Text>Massive Photon Turret</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17803</Index>
			<Text>Massive Photon Cannons mounted on a turret platform. These bigger cannons fire larger Photon torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17804</Index>
			<Text>Improved Phased Rapid Energy Turret</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17805</Index>
			<Text>This turret will unleash rapid fire energy projectiles that will penetrate whatever shields the enemy may have, along with doing twice the damage to armor. It has a medium to long range.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- 4x4 beam  turret tech  description -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17806</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Fusion Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17807</Index>
			<Text>Fusion particle beams gain increased damage over laser beams, but are much less efficient. This particular model is mounted on a swivel to achieve a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17808</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Phasor Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17809</Index>
			<Text>The Heavy Phasor Beam Turret provides a devastating dual Phasor beam with a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17810</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Laser Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17811</Index>
			<Text>The Heavy Laser Beam Turret provides a dual Laser beam with a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- shape memory -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17812</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Small</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17813</Index>
			<Text>A more advanced version of the initial Shape Memory Technology. Mass is unchanged.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17814</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Small</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17815</Index>
			<Text>The most advanced Shape Memory Internal bulkhead we currently possess. It can withstand powerful internal explosions.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17816</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17817</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Large</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17818</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17819</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Large</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Metal internal bulkheads -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>17820</Index>
			<Text>Improved Internal Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17821</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Original Internal Bulkhead. It is more durable and resists explosions.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17822</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Internal Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17823</Index>
			<Text>This is a more advanced version of the Improved Internal Bulkhead. It is even more durable and has better explosive resistance.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17824</Index>
			<Text>Improved Reinforced Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17825</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Original Reinforced Bulkhead. It is more durable and resists explosions.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17826</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Reinforced Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17827</Index>
			<Text>This is a more advanced version of the Improved Reinforced Bulkhead. It is even more durable and has better explosive resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armor Piercing Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17828</Index>
			<Text>Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17829</Index>
			<Text>Armor Piercing III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17830</Index>
			<Text>Kinetic projectiles will pass through the first Medium sized armor (or 2 small) module encountered. The armor will take no damage.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17831</Index>
			<Text>Kinetic projectiles will pass through the first Large sized armor (or 3 small) module encountered. The armor will take no damage.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- fighter Rockets -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17832</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Rockets I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17833</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Rockets II</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17834</Index>
			<Text>Rockets are unguided, fast projectiles with high payloads stored in pods.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17835</Index>
			<Text>Increased sized and damage Rocket pod technology.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17836</Index>
			<Text>Hydra Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17837</Index>
			<Text>Talon Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17838</Index>
			<Text>Hydra rocket pods are very small, able to be mounted on most of our smallest ships. They fire a barrage of quick moving rockets which deal slightly extra damage towards armor.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17839</Index>
			<Text>Talon Rockets are an improvement over the Hydra Rockets. The pod is slightly larger, has higher range, and deals more damage. In addition, they are very effective against armor.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Armored Defense -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17840</Index>
			<Text>Reactive HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17841</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Reactive Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17842</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17843</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Ceramic Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17844</Index>
			<Text>Composite HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17845</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Composite Alloys Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17846</Index>
			<Text>Crystal HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17847</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Crystal Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17848</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17849</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Hyper Active Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Class V and VII shields -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17850</Index>
			<Text>Class V Shield</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17851</Index>
			<Text>Class VII Shield</Text>
		</Token>
				<Token>
			<Index>17852</Index>
			<Text>This is a massive shield for its size, with more protection range and more shielding</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17853</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Shielding III</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17854</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve the output of our Class V shields, along with adding Composite Alloy armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17855</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Canopy Shield</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17856</Index>
			<Text>The best Canopy Shield Generator we can safely install on a starship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17857</Index>
			<Text>Canopy Shielding III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17858</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve the output of our Canopy shields, along with adding Active Armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Medium Nano Ordnance -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17859</Index>
			<Text>Nano Ordnance Locker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17860</Index>
			<Text>A larger version of our small nano ordnance locker. The larger space means fewer walls, making it more efficient. It holds more ordnance than 4 smaller nano lockers, but produces a dangerous localized explosion if destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Home Defense -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17861</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17862</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 4 Home Defense Fighters</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17863</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 4 Fighters that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Fighters available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17864</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17865</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 16 Home Defense Fighters</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17866</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 16 Fighters that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Fighters available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17867</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17868</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 3 Home Defense Corvettes</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17869</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 3 Corvettes that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Corvettes available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17870</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17871</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 9 Home Defense Corvettes</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17872</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 9 Corvettes that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Corvettes available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17873</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17874</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 2 Home Defense Frigates</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17875</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 2 Frigates that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Frigates available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17876</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17877</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 4 Home Defense Frigates</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17878</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 4 Frigates that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Frigates available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- money description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17879</Index>
			<Text>+1 Credit per Colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Laser Beams -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17880</Index>
			<Text>Laser Beams</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17881</Index>
			<Text>A laser is a device that emits light through a process of optical amplification based on the stimulated emission of electromagnetic radiation. The term "laser" originated as an acronym for "light amplification by stimulated emission of radiation". A laser differs from other sources of light in that it emits light coherently. Spatial coherence allows a laser to be focused to a tight spot, which with enough power, can be a deadly weapon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Remnant Fighter Shield -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17882</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Fighter Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17883</Index>
			<Text>An Advanced shield used by Remnant Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fast Fighter shields -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17884</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17885</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Standard Fighter Shield. It has a much faster recharge rate, but it needs more time before recharge starts.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17886</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17887</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved and somwhat larger version of the Fast Fighter Shield. After a decently long cool down, it can recharge very quickly.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Module HP bonus -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17888</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 5% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17889</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 10% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17890</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 15% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17891</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 20% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17892</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 25% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- weapons and event weapons -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17901</Index> 
		  <Text>Prototype energy beam weapon</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17902</Index> 
		  <Text>This is our first attempt in creating reliable energy beam weapon, it is crude, but should be effective.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17903</Index> 
		  <Text>Advanced Flak Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17904</Index> 
		  <Text>Using an improved type of barrel and loading mechanism, Advanced flak cannons improve range, velocity and damage over the previous versions.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17905</Index> 
		  <Text>Advanced Dual Flak Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17906</Index> 
		  <Text>This is our first attempt in creating reliable energy beam weapon, it is crude, but should be effective.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17907</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>With the introduction of new technologies, our efforts in the creation of a powerful beam have been made successful. We managed to create some new experimental phasor weapons, but since we do not fully understand our discovery, these weapons are not perfectly optimized.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17908</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Dual Phasors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17909</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Dual Phasors are our first venture into the creation a dual beam weapon. Unfortunately, the inherent instability of the powerful dual beams limits their maximum range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17910</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Phasor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17911</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Early Phasor prototype, its pure destructive power usually comes with the price of increased size. As a side effect, the extended length of this beam weapon has increased its maximum range, and also mysteriously amplified its mass repulsion effect.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- S_cannon -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17912</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>S cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17913</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Supersonic Stabilized Cannon enhanced with our newest autoloader systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17914</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The Supersonic Stabilized Cannon shoots projectiles at very high velocity. It also features impressive reload times.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- RAD -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17915</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Rotating Atom Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17916</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>An Energy gatling weapon. Designed to continuously rotate massive barrel heads to prevent overheating due to rapid fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17917</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>R.A.D. can shoot Armor Penetating rounds in rapid succession, so long as the ship can provide the needed power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- ScrappyBeam --> 
		<Token>
		  <Index>17918</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>ScrappyBeam.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17919</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This antiquated beam weapon design was previously abandoned due to its lower overall damage potential.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17920</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This weapon may not initially appear impressive when considering the weak damage potential, but as it turns out, it's very good at damaging shields and disrupting onboard power flow.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energizer3x3 -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17921</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Energizer.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17922</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A giant single beam system mounted on a turret.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17923</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The unique design of this large beam system gives it an interesting side effect. Thanks to more densely packed particles within the magnetized stream, there is a slight lock-on effect when multiplying the mass of the target, making tracking more precise.</Text>

		</Token>
		<!-- RemnantNuker -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17924</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>RemnantNuker.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17925</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A compact weapon of mass destruction.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17926</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>For a missile of this size, it's a strikingly devastating weapon. Not only does it melt armor, but it also emits a deadly EMP blast.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Magnetrom -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17927</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Magnetrom</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17928</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A weapon designed around its energized missile warhead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17929</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The sole purpose of the Magnetrom is to swiftly destroy enemy shields, thereby overloading the vulnerable ship's electronics and massively draining any stored power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- TritaniumMissiles-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17930</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Tritanium Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17931</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Missiles constructed from an incredibly durable material.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17932</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Tritanium Missiles are a straightforward weapon. A missile that can receive massive amounts of damage, yet still deliver its payload to the target.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Enforcer -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17933</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Enforcer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17934</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A highly advanced Kinetic weapon that uses energy to propel the shells.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17935</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The Enforcer is a rapid fire weapon system. It requires both power and ordnance to shoot.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cyclone -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17936</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Cyclone</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17937</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A prototype weapon, created in an effort to bridge the gap between energy and ordnance based cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17938</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Cyclone represents the worst and best of both worlds. It features high projectile speeds, great damage, extensive range, and a low cool down, but it requires substantial amounts of power and ordnance to fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- AtomizingBattery -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17939</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Atomizing Battery</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17940</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A heavy artillery energy cannon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17941</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A weapon specifically designed to support long range engagements, providing firepower from the back lines.</Text>

		</Token>
		<!-- Black matter weaponry-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17942</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Dark Matter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17943</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This ingenious weapon utilizes Dark Matter as a projectile. The process to confine and stabilize such a force was made successful by transferring small amounts of Dark Matter from our collectors, then wrapping them into their own individualized charges that can be loaded into a projectile chamber. Upon impact, they release their devastating power.</Text>

		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17944</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The most compact Dark Matter cannon. A fixed position cannon that fires small bursts of stabilized Dark Matter. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17945</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Dark Matter turret. Fires in semi-rapid succession. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17946</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Heavy Dark Matter turret with an expanded field of fire coverage. Features a burst weapon firing system. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17947</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Light Dark Matter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17948</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Dark Matter turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17949</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Heavy Dark Matter turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- StorageShield -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17950</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Integrated Storage Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17951</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Shield module with integrated capacitors for better efficiency.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17952</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The integration of capacitors into this shield module has yielded an improvement in shield strength. Provides a small additional benefit of storing some ship-wide power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- AncientArmor -->
		 <Token>
		  <Index>17953</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Ancient Armors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17954</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Small Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17955</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Medium Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token> 
		   <Token>
		  <Index>17956</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Large Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17957</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A very durable piece of Ancient Armor. Can be used both as an internal bulkhead, or as external armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17958</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Ancient armor is covered in a gold-like coating. Each armor module is made of smaller pieces that tear off when struck.</Text>
		</Token> 
		<Token>
			<Index>17959</Index>
			<Text>Abandoned Warehouse</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17960</Index>
			<Text>Your ship detected an abandoned warehouse on the surface, send troops to investigate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Underhive -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17961</Index>
			<Text>Shady places are perfect ground to gamble. With right connections we can make a profit.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17962</Index>
			<Text>+0.4 Max Population, +2 Production per Richness</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17963</Index>
			<Text>Underhive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17964</Index>
			<Text>The underhive is the most run-down city on the planet where most of the rules are created by Corsair gangs. It is a difficult place to live where the power has long been turned off. People rule through fear and shun the rich that live in the capital.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17965</Index>
			<Text>You can't stop the underhive, and the smugglers keep profiting from it.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17966</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Computing II</Text>
		</Token>			
		<Token>
			<Index>17967</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Computing III</Text>
		</Token>					
		<Token>
			<Index>17968</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17969</Index>
			<Text>Due to the small size of our platforms, the creation of compact orbital weapons now seems to be a necessity. Such weapons would be able to fire in all directions, but as a result we will only be able to install them on our small and heavy platforms. They will feature a high range 360 degree field of fire, and will be armed with kinetic projectile rounds.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17970</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons II</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17971</Index>
			<Text>With advancements in weapons technology, we can develop an improved version of our previous platform kinetic cannons. This Mk2 Orbital Kinetic Cannon will fire faster rounds, have an even higher range, and deal more damage than its predecessor.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17972</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17973</Index>
			<Text>With the success of our previous platform cannons, our engineers have determined that the best path forward in platform weaponry would be the creation of a high-powered, extremely compact cannon. It will deal even more damage, have an incredibly high range, and even higher projectile speed. The longer reload time should make it worth it.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17997</Index>
			<Text>Clean World</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17998</Index>
			<Text>In peaceful times, our people had no need for massive factories. Steady growth and a clean environment were always our way of life. +1 homeworld fertility</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17999</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- hulls tech description -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>18000</Index>
			<Text>Drone</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18001</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18002</Index>
			<Text>Our first fighter hull provides the basic needs of the military. However, in order to expand our tactical options, we can invest time and research into the designing of another, larger fighter hull.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18003</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18004</Index>
			<Text>We can develop yet another fighter hull, designed to be used as a heavy fighter.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18005</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18006</Index>
			<Text>Our first Corvette hull was a success. We can now design a heavier, larger corvette hull that will add more diversity to our ship arsenal.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18007</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18008</Index>
			<Text>Furthering the diversity of our Corvette hulls can help us overcome future military challenges.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18009</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18010</Index>
			<Text>We can research a new frigate hull. It may be an extension of our current frigate hull, or even a brand new design. Regardless, it will have more potential.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18011</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18012</Index>
			<Text>Frigates can play a major part in a fleet. They can even be launched from a carrier ship, assuming the carrier is large enough. We can design an upgrade, or a brand new frigate hull to further increase our combat options.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18013</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18014</Index>
			<Text>Cruisers are the backbone of any fleet. It is recommended that we research heavier cruiser types in order to keep up with the military's demands.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18015</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18016</Index>
			<Text>In order to strengthen our core fleets, we believe developing another, heavier cruiser design would be a good decision.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18017</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18018</Index>
			<Text>We can design a larger Battleship to command and coordinate our fleets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18019</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18020</Index>
			<Text>A larger Battleship, almost as big as a Titan, can be researched and introduced into the war effort.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18021</Index>
			<Text>Titan Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18022</Index>
			<Text>We can now design the marvel of our empire. This ship design is around twice the size of the first Titan we have designed. This Super Titan will proudly represent the height of our Empire's military might. The production cost of these ships is so high that building one would be a massive undertaking. Building too many might be an unwise decision.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18023</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannons II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18024</Index>
			<Text>Pure destructive power, incarnate. These assault cannons now have less of a penalty against shields, and the energized field around the projectiles grants them a chance at completely penetrating them. They are still quite effective against armor, though it is lessened compared to our previous weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18025</Index>
			<Text>Assault Disintegrator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18026</Index>
			<Text>The damage output of these monstrosities can overwhelm any enemy ship, as well as their own ship's power reserves.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18027</Index> <!-- Dauntless preferred envs -->
		  <Text> prosper in Terran worlds, and like Steppe and Tundra and Ice worlds. They dislike Barren, Desert Swamp amd Oceanic Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18028</Index>
		  <Text>New line of rocket pods build upon very effective Talon class rockets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Hellstorm systems-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18029</Index>
		  <Text>The most advanced in the storm line of weapons, the Hellstorm delivers a devastating salvo of 6 rockets that now have a substantial chance to penetrate shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18030</Index>
		  <Text>Anti-Fighter Missiles III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18031</Index>
		  <Text>This is the top of the line in short range missile systems, using the newest technologies in missile structures to improve their utility, range, and most importantly, damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18032</Index>
		  <Text>Hell Storm</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Venom pods-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18033</Index>
		  <Text>Venom Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18034</Index>
		  <Text>This Venom pod is an improvement over the Talon pod in that it fires more missiles per attack, at only slightly lower damage per missile. They also have a slight chance to penetrate enemy shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Nemesis pods-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18035</Index>
		  <Text>Nemesis Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		<Index>18036</Index>
		  <Text>With this extremely deadly rocket pod, we are now able to launch missiles that deal twice the normal damage to armor. Their chance to penetrate shields is also increased.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tactical cannon-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18037</Index>
		  <Text>Tactical Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18038</Index>
		  <Text>Designed almost as an afterthought, our scientists realized we could incorporate advanced subspace mechanics into a smaller cannon, with the only drawback of less extensive damage to enemy armor. This weapon should prove very useful in cases where the massive cannons are simply too large.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- assault cannons type 10 & 20-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18039</Index>
		  <Text>Assault Cannon Type10</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18040</Index>
		  <Text>A prototype leftover from our testing, this miniaturized assault cannon proved reliable enough for use in circumstances where space is limited. Although it lacks the pure damage potential of the larger Type74, it should still be useful as a primary weapon on our medium sized vessels. It features explosive ammunition.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18041</Index>
		  <Text>Assault Cannon Type20</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18042</Index>
		  <Text>A dedicated small assault cannon, only slightly longer than the Type10. The mounting rail has been over-energized in order to supply the necessary power to the miniature assault driver, and as a result, it can no longer be mounted internally on our ships. It features explosive ammunition.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Dissolver_Torpedo -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18043</Index>
		  <Text>Dissolver Torpedo Tube</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18044</Index>
		  <Text>Large torpedo caring a large number of smaller mirv missiles with energized warheads to counter heavily shielded targets. Delayed ignition of mirv missiles makes them pass the initial target and turn around, hitting enemy ship engines. </Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18045</Index>
		  <Text>Gain an empire-wide 10% bonus to the amount of power that is stored in dedicated power cells</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18046</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced Railgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18047</Index>
		  <Text>This new Railgun serves as a direct upgrade to the older Railgun. It has better range, damage and speed.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18048</Index>
		  <Text>Structure</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18049</Index>
		  <Text>This simple structure is used as a "filler" for ships which do not require more module functionality</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>18050</Index>
		  <Text>Planetary Education Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18051</Index>
		  <Text>This buildings provides tools which enhance our Scientists' and Engineers' capabilities.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18052</Index>
		  <Text>Planetary Sanitation Center</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18053</Index>
		  <Text>Planetary Transportation Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18054</Index>
		  <Text>This building controls and coordinates advanced transportation methods in the colony.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18055</Index>
		  <Text>Planetary Sanitation Center</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>18056</Index>
		  <Text>New Sanitation techniques can help maintain our colony's health and protect it from new type of Xeno-Bacteria.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>18057</Index>
		  <Text>Shields Efficiency V1</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
		  <Index>18058</Index>
		  <Text>Improved Shield projection technologies can increase the strength of our Shields by 10% across the board (Planetry Shields included).</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>18059</Index>
		  <Text>Increase Shields Strength by 10%</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18060</Index>
		  <Text>Shields Efficiency V2</Text>
		</Token>									
		<Token>
		  <Index>18061</Index>
		  <Text>Shields Efficiency V3</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>18062</Index>
		  <Text>Shields Efficiency V4</Text>
		</Token>							
		<Token>
		  <Index>18063</Index>
		  <Text>Shields Efficiency V5</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18064</Index> <!-- tech -->
			<Text>Planetary Shielding</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18065</Index>
			<Text>We can create a bigger shield protecting the planet from bombardment for quite sometime. The down side will be cost and maintenance of the shield.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Orbital Missiles -->
		<Token>
			<Index>18066</Index> 
			<Text>Orbital Missiles I</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18067</Index> 
			<Text>Long range missiles which can be launched from our Orbital assets to provide some defense from enemy invasion fleets. These missiles are somewhat crude and not mounted on turrets, but can be effective.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>18068</Index> 
			<Text>Orbital Missiles II</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18069</Index> 
			<Text>Bigger Orbital Missiles with multiple warheads and longer range. Can better face the threat of bigger invasion ships.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>18070</Index> 
			<Text>Orbital Missiles III</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18071</Index> 
			<Text>These Orbital Missiles contain mor warheads and terminal velocity increase. This means that at a certain range, the missile warhead will lose guidance but vastly increase its speed, making it harder to intercept my missile defense systems.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Smart Missiles -->
		<Token>
			<Index>18072</Index> 
			<Text>Smart Missiles</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18073</Index> 
			<Text>Advanced guidance systems can be installed in missiles to enable them to seek new targets if their original target is not valid.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18074</Index> 
			<Text>Our missiles will now  seek new targets if their original target is not valid.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Tratanium HMG -->
		<Token>
			<Index>18075</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18076</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Tritanium Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>18077</Index>
			<Text>Canopy Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18078</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Missiles III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18079</Index>
			<Text>We can attempt to create a very large missile system which will launch better Anti Capital Missiles at a high rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18080</Index>
			<Text>Solar Arrays V1</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18081</Index>
			<Text>Our Cybernetic Citizens can be upgraded with Solar Arrays to reduce their production consumption when they are in a colony.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18082</Index>
			<Text>Reduces each colony's production consumption by 10%</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>18083</Index>
			<Text>Upgading our citizen's solar arrays will further reduce their production consumption.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18084</Index>
			<Text>Solar Arrays V2</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18085</Index>
			<Text>Solar Arrays V3</Text>
		</Token>		
				<Token>
			<Index>18086</Index>
			<Text>Solar Arrays V4</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18087</Index>
			<Text>Solar Arrays V5</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Mass Reduction Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>18088</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by a total of 4% across the board.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>18089</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by a total of 8% across the board.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18090</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by a total of 12% across the board.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18091</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by a total of 16% across the board.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18092</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by a total of 20% across the board.</Text>
		</Token>		
	</TokenList>
</LocalizationFile>
