<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>Discover Crashed Ship</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>Unknown defenders</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Before reaching the Crashed Ship, your troops were attacked by unknown enemies and had to fall back, the crashed ship takes off and warps out of the system.</DescriptionText>
       <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Skeleton</string>
        <string>Skeleton</string>
        <string>Skeleton</string>
      </TroopsToSpawn>     
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/remn5.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>What is dead should stay dead!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>6</Chance>
      <TitleText>A unique technology and great peril!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops found a ship, inside on they found a data core with schematics of unknown technology. While removing the data core from the socket, they triggered ship security protocols alarming a dormant Remnant Inhibitor!</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <UnlockTech>RemnantNuker</UnlockTech>       
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
          <string>Remnant Inhibitor</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>       
      <TroopsToSpawn>
      </TroopsToSpawn>      
      <Image>Encounters/techevent2.png</Image> 
      <ConfirmText>This could gone worse.</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>8</Chance>
      <TitleText>A unique technology!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops found a ship, inside on they found a data core with schematics of unknown technology. While removing the data core from the socket, they triggered ship security protocols alarming dormant space defenders.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <UnlockTech>Remnant Studies</UnlockTech>       
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
          <string>Heavy Drone</string>
          <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
          <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
          <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>       
      <TroopsToSpawn>
      </TroopsToSpawn>       
      <Image>Encounters/remn2.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Lets study it!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>Red Alert</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While your troops are examining the wreckage, its computer systems come online and an alarm is tripped by one of your clumsy grunts. Your troops manage to deactivate the alarm and salvage the control system which is valuable on the black market, however a fleet of Remnant vessels jumps into orbit detecting your presence.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Heavy Drone</string>
        <string>Heavy Drone</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>
      <Image>Encounters/remn1.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Retreat!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>30</Chance>
      <TitleText>A sad wreck</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of what is clearly a very, very ancient shipwreck. Time and nature have taken their toll on the wreckage. Even so, there are some curiosities among the wreckage that will have some value on the open market.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>250</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/CrashedShip.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Profit!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Excellent find</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Here you have made an excellent discovery - what appeared from orbit to be a shipwreck was in fact not a wreck at all, but a completely intact alien light frigate! Further examination reveals that it is space worthy and the cargo hold contains a mysterious artifact.</DescriptionText>
      <FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
          <string>Heavy Drone</string>
          <string>Heavy Drone</string>
          <string>Support Drone</string>
      </FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
      <GrantArtifact>true</GrantArtifact>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/remn4.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Oh, lets test those bad boys!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>8</Chance>
      <TitleText>Unstable</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of what is clearly a very, very ancient shipwreck. Time and nature have taken their toll on the wreckage. But even so, scans show its reactor is still functional, leaking more and more antimatter particles by the minute. And, what's that? Oh no. It's about to blow! Your forces quickly evacuate to a safe distance. Soon after, the reactor explodes, destroying the wreckage and severely damaging a large portion of the planet. Planet scans changed : -0.6 Fertility(temporally), -3 habitable tiles.</DescriptionText>
      <NumTilesToMakeUnhabitable>3</NumTilesToMakeUnhabitable>
      <ChangeBaseFertility>-0.6</ChangeBaseFertility>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/CrashedShip.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>What a disaster.</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Precious cargo</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of what is clearly a very, very ancient shipwreck. Time and nature have taken their toll on the wreckage. But even so, scans show its reactor is still functional and providing power to the storage unit, inside your troops found a very rare seed, that was being transported somewhere.</DescriptionText>
      <ReplaceWith>WorldSeed</ReplaceWith>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/CrashedShip2.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Don't eat it!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>2</Chance>
      <TitleText>Space car?</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of a small spacecraft that crashed into the planet a long time ago. From the description of the scans, it seems too small for a spaceship. Even more puzzling is that it has wheels. Could this have been an old automobile of some sort? No, those were never designed to be launched into space.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/CrashedShip.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>This one probably broke few speed limits.</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>
  </PotentialOutcomes>
</ExplorationEvent>