<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>Discover Pirate Treasure</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>
  <Outcome>
      <Chance>12</Chance>
      <TitleText>It's a Trap!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find an entrance to bunker with doors blasted wide open. Corridors are littered with dead bodies with torn limbs, there are clear signs of a battle. Sadly there isn't anything worth of value here and what's worse, nest of Antlions that has made its home here.</DescriptionText>
       <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
      </TroopsToSpawn>     
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/1.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Why wont they stay dead for once!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>A Treasure</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces found recently half cleared out rooms, it seems someone beat us to it, though several things were left behind which are valuable.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>1500</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/2.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Shiny Things!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>7</Chance>
      <TitleText>The Boss arrives</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find an entrance to a hidden cave Before they enter it, long range scanner from shuttle their detects a mighty vessel belonging to pirates warping into the system. It seems that the pirates have returned for their hidden treasure. As you troops fall back, they see pirate shuttle landing and taking the treasure from the cave back to their ship.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <PirateShipsToSpawn>
          <string>Corsair Flagship</string>
      </PirateShipsToSpawn>
      <Image>Encounters/pirates3.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Again the Pirates</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>     
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>Pirate Technology?</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find an entrance to a hidden cave and enter it. What they found is truly astonishing. It seems that the pirates have created an untested tech. Unfortunately, it seems that the pirate fleet left here might not let you go unharmed, unless you paid them for protection recently.</DescriptionText>
      <UnlockTech>Ancient Shield Technology</UnlockTech>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <PirateShipsToSpawn>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
          <string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
      </PirateShipsToSpawn>       
      <Image>Encounters/techevent2.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>This is now ours!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>It's a trap!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find an entrance to a hidden cave and enter it only to find that it is empty. One of the troops find a note that says: "Even in my death i outsmart you. You will never find the treasure. Take 2 credits instead, hahaha!". When your troops exit the cave, they find a big swarm of giant insects!</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>2</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>       
      <SelectRandomPlanet>true</SelectRandomPlanet>
      <SpawnBuildingOnPlanet>Treasure</SpawnBuildingOnPlanet>
      <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
          <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
      </TroopsToSpawn>
      <Image>Encounters/6.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Lets play a game of tag!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>     

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Military Salvage</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find an entrance to a hidden cave and enter it. They find 2 stolen Frigates, not even painted with pirate signs. Your Troops bring them into orbit.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>       
      <FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
        <string>Gunboat Ballista Mk1</string>
          <string>Gunboat Ballista Mk1</string>
      </FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
      <Image>Encounters/pirates1.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Stealing from the thieves!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>     

      <Outcome>
      <Chance>11</Chance>
      <TitleText>A artifact</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces found recently half cleared out rooms, it seems someone beat us to it, but they still might have missed something. After thoroughly scanning the complex, your troops found a hidden room that contains an ancient artifact.</DescriptionText>
      <GrantArtifact>true</GrantArtifact>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/techevent1.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Haste is a waste!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>A seed!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Upon entering the hidden facility, your forces notice that various rooms have been ransacked, locks broken and packages torn open, their contents spilt over the floor. Someone went through this place in a hurry. \n Checking the facility, one of our technicians remarks that there is a hidden room. It is just barely visible on our recently improved scanning equipment. Had we come here a year before with the older equipment, we would have surely missed it. The technician bypasses the electronic entrance key to the room and discovers a room with a carefully managed humid atmosphere. Inside it, the sapling of an extraordinary tree is being nurtured. \n \n World seed found!.</DescriptionText>
      <ReplaceWith>WorldSeed</ReplaceWith>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <Image>Encounters/3.png</Image>
      <ConfirmText>Haste is a waste!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>
  </PotentialOutcomes>
</ExplorationEvent>